Yuki, you here?
Oh, Masachika-kun. Thank you for coming.
No problem. What's this about?
You could start with some pleasantries.
How about, "Sorry, did you wait long?"
Sorry, did you wait long?
Yeah, you really kept me waiting!
You two sure get along.
Didn't know you were here, Alya.
I sure am. Sorry for being the third wheel.
Welp...
This jerk set me up.
So, you want me to help
sort out everything in storage?
Yes.
Hup.
Of course you'd be at home doing this.
I guess.
Could you help me out for a second here?
Hmm? Board games?
Here.
Thank you kindly.
I see cards, too.
We use these for school festival events.
I also happened to play during the new
student council's get-together the other day.
Huh. Who won, by the way?
Um... I suppose I was technically the winner...
Figures.
Less chatting, more working.
Oops, sorry.
Pardon us, Alisa-san.
Give me attention, too.
Come to me. Come to me.
What is she thinking? Isn't that embarrassing?!
I'm throwing myself at him, and he has no idea.
Come to me. Come to me.
Student Council Office
Great work, Masachika-kun.
Thanks. You were a big help.
Sure.
What, already done?
Yes.
Kuze-kun helped us out.
Oh, so you're Kuze.
I'm Kenzaki, the student council president.
Sometimes
in Russian
Hides Her
Feelings
Alya Sometimes Hides
Her Feelings in Russian
I've heard lots about you and how talented you are.
Episode 2
So Much For Childhood Friends
Gee, thanks.
Yeah, he definitely has an aura about him.
No wonder he's our superstar president.
See you later, then.
Hold up.
I'd feel bad sending you off
empty-handed after all your help.
Let me buy you dinner.
It's fine. Appreciate the thought, though.
Why not accept?
You won't have dinner ready for you
when you get home, anyway.
Huh?
How do you know what he has going on at home?
We go way back.
Yeah?
Perfect, then. You two join us,
Suou and Kujo Junior.
Thank you for offering.
Very well.
Seriously?
It's not like a casual diner costs much!
Anyway, I'm impressed you finished so quickly.
I was expecting it to take until tomorrow.
Masachika-kun's amazing.
He can handle physical labor
and paperwork like it's nothing,
and he's an expert emcee and negotiator.
Quit hyping me up.
It's not often Suou goes
overboard with the praise.
Kuze, any interest
in joining the student council?
Sorry, but I'm done with
student council work forever.
I had enough in middle school.
Hmm. Being part of the student council
at our high school is certainly a lot of work,
but it comes with its own benefits.
If I may be blunt,
it'll have a massive effect
on your recommendation.
Hate to break it to you,
but I'm not much of a go-getter.
Come on, please join us.
Let's run for office together again.
Don't suggest that so casually!
And heck, do you even need me?
You're a shoo-in to be the next president anyway.
But I want to run the
student council with you.
Nope! Can't be bothered!
I must correct you, Kuze.
Suou is far from being a shoo-in.
We have other candidates.
Chief among them is Kujo Junior over here.
Alya?
Yeah. I'll be running against
Suou-san next year.
Here's your order!
Thanks for the meal.
Sure.
Suou and I are going this way.
You walk Kujo Junior home, Kuze.
Sure.
Okay, shall we go?
It's fine. You don't need to walk me.
You know that's not gonna fly.
Alya.
What?
Are you really gonna run
for student council president?
I am. I said as much earlier.
Huh...
I'll be fine from here. Thanks.
Yeah?
Bye.
Welcome back.
Did you walk Alya-san home?
What're you doing here?
I'm staying here tonight.
News to me.
It's breaking now.
Teach Me How to Love 2
Ah, yes, an unknown hot guy
walking with the heroine.
Gotta be her brother.
Older, from the looks of it.
Man, that should be obvious.
Why won't the protag realize?
Uh, you're one to talk.
Huh?
You're one to talk when you're pretending
to be my childhood friend in school.
What? It's not a lie!
Do you even know what a childhood friend is?
Someone you got along with growing up, right?
Exactly!
That includes siblings!
"Childhood friend," "otaku buddy,"
and "sister" can all be true at the same time!
What a weird interpretation.
More like a big-brain interpretation
of constantly evolving language!
Whoa, timeout!
It really was the heroine's big bro with her.
Classic trope.
He's kissing the heroine now.
For real?!
For real.
Damn, we're getting some wincest.
Wait, hold on.
Think about it. They've gotta be
step-siblings or something.
You moron!
It's only good when they're blood-related!
Suou Yuki
Masachika's actual
little sister
Bwof!
Good morning, my brother.
It stopped being good a few seconds ago.
Come on, now. Your dearest little sister's
waking you up with love and warmth.
Rejoice.
Yeah, I'm not letting you spin this.
This is just DV.
DV? "Dear Venus"?
Aw, big bro, you love me so!
Domestic violence!
Fine, have it your way.
Next time, I'll hide under your bed
and grab your leg as you get out.
What are you even trying to be in life?
Yeesh. Get off already.
Why?
Getting a stiffy?
Die.
All right, rise and shine.
You have a date with your dearest little sis!
Animated Movie
Exciting Boogaloo
Space Girl Chii
Yeah, that was pretty good.
So good.
The movie-exclusive relationship moments
that are never in the TV show...
So good!
Okay, time to rewatch!
Yeah, no! We're supposed to go shopping!
Unhand me! The movie is calling my name!
Whoa! Quit lining up for tickets!
I've been wanting a new summery dress.
But I'm about to go broke buying merch.
Ouch! This is 15,000 yen?!
Women's fashion costs a lot
for every inch of fabric.
You don't say.
As an aside, sister of mine.
What is it, beloved brother of mine?
Is it just me who's been seeing a silver
something in the corner of my eye?
Not just you, my brother.
Figures.
You've undone your ponytail and
switched to prim-and-proper rich girl mode.
I noticed a long time before you did, bro.
Really? When?
Pretty soon after we came down to this floor.
That long ago? I'm impressed.
Hmph. I possess a hyper sixth sense
for detecting the gaze of people I know.
Seriously?
Doesn't saying that make you cringe?
I'm cringing hard.
Nothing to be smug about!
Now, how do I solve this problem at hand?
My, Alisa-san?
Sister of mine!
Hey, it's Alya. What a coincidence.
Y-Yes, quite the coincidence.
I spotted you two a few moments ago,
but I couldn't find the right time to say hi.
"Few moments ago," my ass.
"Few moments ago," my foot.
What brings you here, Alisa-san?
Oh, clothes shopping.
Is that so? Have you had lunch already?
No, not yet.
In that case, would you like to
join us? We're about to—
Hold up! Are you thinking of
taking Alya to that restaurant?
Is that a problem?
You were looking forward to it.
It's clearly a problem!
We should go somewhere else
if we're taking Alya.
What? What's the problem?
Do you dislike spicy food?
Spicy food?
Pon Curry
Mild
No, I don't particularly.
Pon Curry
Mild
We were about to go to a restaurant
that serves spicy ramen.
If you don't dislike spicy food, join us.
Stop downplaying it.
Alya, let me be straight with you.
It's not just spicy. That place
serves super spicy ramen.
I'll go.
You don't have to come with us
if you don't want to.
What, do you have
a problem with my presence?
That's not what I mean.
Hell's
Cauldron
Hell's Cauldron
Is this it?
It is.
It's called Hell's Cauldron?
You said it's a ramen place, right?
It very much is.
Why does it have "hell" in the name?
Rest assured, it's in all
the dishes' names, too.
That so?
Having second thoughts?
Of course not!
I simply needed a moment
to process how unique this place is.
I see.
Welcome!
Table for three? This way, please.
Hell's Cauldron
Our trademark three stages of hell
Pool of
Blood Hell
Our most popular offering
Pincushion
Hell
Piercing heat
Infinite Hell
Makes even the demons of hell squirm
I have no idea what any of this means.
Yep.
Pool of Blood Hell is a ramen
with bright-red soup.
It has the least heat on this menu.
Pincushion Hell is so hot,
it feels like your tongue is being
pierced by countless needles.
What's this "Infinite Hell" at the bottom?
Apparently, it's so spicy that your entire
mouth just goes completely numb.
I think I'll go with Pool of Blood Hell.
Can't get too adventurous with your order
when it's your first time at a restaurant.
R-Right. It's good to start with the basics.
Are you both ordering that?
In that case, I'll have the same thing myself.
Three Pools of Blood for Table 5!
You're dressed quite
boyishly today, Suou-san.
It caught me by surprise.
It is a day off, so I went with this for
a change of pace in my private time.
Yeah? "Private time," huh?
You see, I was in bed
with Masachika-kun this morning.
In bed... with him?
Yes. And because I wanted to wear
something different today,
I asked him to let me borrow this shirt.
What's the meaning of this?
Wait, she just showed up at my place,
entered my room, and jumped
in my bed all by herself, believe me!
Oh, really?
Not buying it, huh?
Here's your order.
Three Pools of Blood.
Here we go.
Let's dig in before it gets soggy.
Yeah.
R-Right...
You okay there, Alya?
Yeah, this is very good.
Oh, this is great.
Isn't it? The chilies accentuate
the ingredients very well.
Help, it hurts.
Seriously, Alya, you don't have to
push yourself.
What are you talking about? I said it's good.
Uh, you said "it hurts."
I can't...
Mama...
Alya—
How do you like it, Alisa-san?
This is delicious.
That's great. I'm so happy to hear that
you enjoy super spicy food, too.
At this restaurant,
you can use this Devil's Tear seasoning
to make your food even spicier.
Would you like to try it?
Hey, Yuki...
She's doing this on purpose!
Y-Yeah, I think I will.
Wait, Alya. You should really rethink this.
One little drop won't kill me.
You alive, Alya?
Where's Suou-san?
She ran off, saying she had something to buy.
Oh.
You okay?
What do you mean?
You know what I mean.
Want some ice cream?
I do.
Mom, I want chocolate!
Say, Alya.
What?
Why do you wanna be
student council president?
Because I want to.
Do I really need a reason to aim higher?
Do you have a running mate?
I don't.
But that won't be a problem.
I don't need anyone.
Uh, that's not how it works.
The rules say you have to run as a pair.
I just need a vice president on paper, right?
I'll try to find some
random person to support me.
Yeah?
If only you would...
Dad...
Mom... I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry!
Kuze-kun, do you have any plans after this?
Nah, not really.
What about Suou-san?
I mean, we could just meet up later.
Yeah?
Then come help me out.
With what?
Oh, you did say you wanted to shop for clothes.
That's right.
You sure about that?
A dude helping a girl pick out clothes?
That kinda implies a close relationship.
Really?
Oh...
Alya doesn't have friends
to go clothes shopping with.
So she doesn't get how it all works.
Yeah, let me help.
What's gotten into you?
We're friends, after all.
Something about that
doesn't sit right.
Don't worry about it.
Why'd he suddenly start being nice to me?
Wait, does he think I don't stand
a chance of becoming president?
Stuff your pity!
Okay, I'll go change! Tell me what you think!
You got it.
I'll blow his mind with my fashion show
and show him who's boss!
Wait a second. He might hear me
changing outside.
Kuze-kun! Move farther away!
Gotcha.
Yes, I look nice, if I do say so myself.
All right!
What if he doesn't react?
Oh, it's fine, I guess.
Hmph! Try it,
and I'll slap your mouth off!
What do you say?
Wow, so pretty!
Oh, you look great.
That outfit ups your elegance and femininity
and makes you look even prettier than usual.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Okay, next.
Huh? What was that?!
He praised the heck out of me!
I can't! I can't handle this embarrassment!
How does she do this all the time?!
Teenage couple?
How cute.
He said I was pretty...
He said I was pretty!
I didn't know he had it in him
to compliment a girl right.
I'm impressed.
He's kind of... used to it?
Her outfit today was pretty boyish.
What do you say about this?
Now you look really cool.
You're more hot than cute,
so I think it suits you.
O-Oh?
You think? Thanks.
Okay, next.
Wow, that's lovely!
Sexy suits you, too.
Pretty.
So pretty!
You're so pretty.
Pretty
Wow, this feels so good!
What next?
This may be a little too revealing.
But I'm sure Kuze-kun will like it.
How about this one?
Wow, Alisa-san, you're so daring.
Yep.
I wanna disappear.
What'd she say?
She wants to disappear, apparently.
Hah, what a big baby.
Who're you supposed to be?
See you Monday, Alya.
Today was fun. We should hang out again.
Yeah, we should. Bye.
What was I thinking with that skimpy skirt?
They must think I'm a skank!
Wait, why'd they get off at the same station?
Huh?
What?!