Sometimes
in Russian
Hides Her
Feelings
Alya Sometimes Hides
Her Feelings in Russian
Episode 3
And So They Met
I'm back.
Welcome home, Alya-chan!
Hug.
I'm home, Masha.
Come on! I told you to
call me Onee-chan in Japan!
No, not after all this time.
Boo, you meanie!
You seem kinda down.
Did something happen?
No? Not really.
Lies. You can't deceive my eyes.
Tell me, what happened?
It's really not a big deal.
I just met Kuze-kun
and his childhood friend. That's all.
Ah, him.
What?
You just get really
worked up when it comes to him.
I see.
Finally, a boy who can move
your heart has showed up, huh?
What's that mean?
You like this Kuze-kun, don't you?
I don't know what gave you that silly idea,
but he and I aren't like that.
We are, uh...
Right, we are friends.
Oh, yeah? How did you become friends, though?
I know you hate indifferent slackers.
Well, yeah...
6 Years Ago
Vladivostok
Split up into groups
and write a report on local businesses.
The group with the best report
will receive a prize!
So, I'll handle the clothes boutique and the bakery.
Alya, you visit the florist and the butcher.
Okay, got it.
If I'm in it,
I'm in it to win.
Excuse me!
Hey, missy. On an errand?
No, this is schoolwork.
We have to look into local businesses
and find out about
what their work involves.
Oh, this is the place.
Excuse me!
The assignment?
Oh, sorry. Haven't started yet.
What?
But why?
Writing up the report takes time, so we need to hurry.
There's still a week left. We'll be fine.
No, we won't!
Besides, this is easy.
A clothes boutique sells clothes, a bakery sells bread.
Right?
Whoa, she's writing up whole essays!
You gotta chill out, girl.
Alya, will we have to recite all of this?
Why won't you take this seriously?
If you got such a problem with us, you can do this alone!
We won't win if we don't put in the effort!
H-Hey!
S-Stop! Knock it off!
For the group assignment,
the best report belongs to...
Group B!
Yeah! Hooray!
If only the others
had taken it as seriously...
No, that's not it.
I was wrong to expect anything from them.
I feel like nobody is ever as driven as I am.
If that's the case,
then I'll just do everything all by myself!
Hey, hey.
Is it true you passed
that crazy difficult transfer exam?
Y-Yeah, I guess I did.
Your Japanese is great, Kujo-san.
Have you lived in Japan before?
Yes, I lived here until five years ago.
Talk to you later, Kujo-san!
He slept through that racket?
Hey, the warning bell's ringing.
Oh, you the transfer student who did
that speech at the opening ceremony?
Yes, that's me.
I'm Alisa Mikhailovna Kujo. Nice to meet you.
Hi. I'm Kuze Masachika.
Nice to meet you too...
Oh?
Heya, Hikaru. Didn't know
you were in this class.
I am.
Takeshi's here too, by the way.
So he is.
Science
Crap, I forgot my textbook.
Sorry. Hikaru, Show me yours.
Sure.
Science
P.E.
That was rough, huh?
I know, right?
Wha...
P.E.
Math
I guess slackers are everywhere,
even in prestigious schools like this one.
School Festival starts in 14 days!
Haunted House
Confirmed!
Uh...
We're gonna need shutters to make the paths.
How are we getting costumes for all the ghosts?
Wait, wait! One thing at a time!
Man, I had no idea it'd be so much work.
Same.
Not going home yet, Kujo-san?
No, I'll work on this some more.
Yeah?
See you, then.
Are we gonna make it?
Who knows? But it's just
a school festival, anyway.
No point getting all worked up over it.
It's happening again.
Ouch!
I just want to do the best I can...
and not throw in the towel.
If that's going to leave me all alone,
then fine, whatever.
Figured you'd still be here.
Kuze-kun? What are you doing here?
Hey. Just had a few things to take care of.
You should go home, Kujo-san.
We can all get together
and handle this stuff tomorrow.
Don't mind me.
I'll go home after I get some more done.
Yeah? Well, uh...
The handicrafts club agreed to
help us out with the costumes.
Huh?
Check this out.
Permission to stay overnight at school.
A special event like that will light a fire
under the unmotivated folks, too.
How did you pull that off?
Asked the former student council
president to pull some strings.
And I told the handicrafts club
our boys would help with their work.
If we frame it as a chance
to show off to the girls there,
the boys will gladly go for it.
That's the deal,
so you should really call it a day.
There's no point grinding away all on your own.
What do you mean, "There's no point"?
I just want to make this a good attraction
if I'm going to be participating in it!
I don't want to put out something shoddy!
I refuse to compromise on the quality!
Haunted
But I know that's just my ego talking!
I get that you all don't care
about it as much as I do!
That's why I'm taking on the load
and putting in all this effort!
Am I doing anything wrong?!
You're putting effort into the wrong things.
Huh?
School festival attractions
aren't meant to be built alone.
The whole point of them is for us all
to work together to create something.
If you wanna make it the best it can be,
then you should be focusing on how to
motivate the whole class, don't you think?
But...
Well, I suppose putting it like that
would only piss you off.
My bad.
I get that you're doing
what you can, and I appreciate it.
I'm leaving.
Great. Have a good night.
What's with him?
What's his problem?!
What's his deal...
Overnight Session!
There you have it!
We'll work on the festival stuff
and have some hide-and-seek and
test-of-courage sessions on school grounds.
We're gonna have
a pre-pre-pre-festival party all of our own!
Yeah!
Hustle!
School festival starts
in 6 days!
Seirei Fall Festival
Best Attraction Award
Class Event Category
Class 3-B
Oh, hey, Kujo-san.
This school can be old-fashioned
in the weirdest ways.
Who still holds a folk dance
for the after-party?
May I sit here?
Sure, but aren't you gonna dance?
I'm sure everyone and their mother
wants to dance with you.
Oh, wait. Do you not know
how to folk dance or something?
Rude. I practiced ballet as a child, you know.
This simplistic dance
won't be a problem in the least.
But I turned everyone down saying
I couldn't dance because I can't be bothered.
Fighting 'em off must've been a pain.
Not really. I'm used to it,
so it wasn't a big deal.
You don't say.
That's our ice princess for you.
What was that?
Wait, you didn't know?
May I have this dance with you?
That's what the others
have taken to calling you lately.
Huh.
You don't sound too pleased about it.
Yeah. That's because I'm not.
Why's that? 'Cause they're
indirectly calling you a loner?
That's not it. Can you stop
with that mocking tone?
Sorry.
The "princess" part is what I take issue with.
Isn't that a compliment?
It makes it sound like I'm a silver-spoon snob.
That's one way to look at it.
Sure, I was born with
above-average looks and talent.
But never once have I coasted by on that alone.
It annoys me when all my efforts
get ignored in favor of my birth.
That makes sense.
I'll make sure not to call you that, then.
Yeah?
Thank you, Kuze-kun.
Hmm? For what?
Can you even dance?
You were right. I was wrong.
If I'd tried to do it all alone,
I would've never gotten to experience
the school festival this way.
Also, I'm sorry for
lashing out at you the other day.
Don't let it bother you.
All I did was file some paperwork.
I didn't put in half the work
you or Takeshi did.
But it does bother me.
I want to apologize for that
and repay you for all this in a tangible way.
Is there anything you want?
"Repay me," eh?
You're not allowed to refuse.
Hmm...
Wait, I got it!
Isn't there a Russian custom where people
call each other by special nicknames?
Diminutives? What about them?
Alisha? Or would it be Aliska?
Alya. That's what my family calls me.
Oh, yeah? How about you give me
permission to call you Alya, then?
Huh? What's in it for you, though?
You're our class's idol,
the apple of everyone's eye.
And I get the glory of being
the only guy who calls you by your nickname!
Are you okay in the head?
Thank you for this glorious gift!
Gross!
E-Excuse me. Kujo-san?
Would you please dance with me?
Hey! Who said you could go first?!
Alisa-san! I've been
interested in you for a while now!
Please dance with me!
Dude, you practically asked her out! No fair!
I'm sorry. I can't dance.
Come on! All you gotta do
is move with the music.
Yeah, you'll be fine!
I can't really dance either!
Just go with the vibes!
Okay, you all need to calm down.
Sorry, boys, she's taken.
Let's go, Alya.
H-Hey!
I can feel my heart about to explode.
Oh, remember what you said?
You used to practice ballet,
so you can pick up folk dancing easily, right?
Y-Yeah?
Let's see what you've got, then,
Princess.
You're on!
Morning, Alya.
Hey, what's up? You're looking
at me like I'm human garbage.
You waste of space.
Sharp-tongued, much?!
Best Attraction Award
Class Event Category
Class 3-B
Just when I'd thought you were so cool last night.
I get it now.
That's what made you fall for him, huh?
What a lovely story!
Again, it's not like that.
Were you even listening to me?
What?
That clearly sounded like
the start of a beautiful love story.
Stop being weird about it.
I told you, we're friends.
Ah, yes, from friends to lovers.
The classic progression.
Sa-kun and I were like that, too.
Weren't we?
All that aside, you get it now.
I know how capable he is, and I trust him.
Boys who get things done
when it counts really do shine, huh?
Sa-kun was the same.
Back when he saved me
from the dog attack, he was so...
Can you go brag about
your love life somewhere else?
Come on, Alya-chan! You big meanie!
Student Council Office
Excuse me.
Hey there, Kuze.
Thanks for coming to help.
Oh, I'm just here to cover for Yuki.
My, so you're Kuze-kun?
I'm Mariya Mikhailovna Kujo.
Alya-chan's big sis
and student council secretary.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Alya's been a great friend to me.
I heard you needed someone
to go shopping with you, Kujo-senpai.
Please, call me Masha.
Any friend of Alya-chan's
is a friend to me, too.
Oh... Masha-san, then.
Very good. Again,
it's a pleasure to meet... you?
Wh-What's wrong?
Kuze-kun, what's your given name?
Huh? It's Masachika,
meaning "together with diplomacy."
Masa... chika?
What's wrong? Is there something behind Kuze?
Prez, shouldn't you ask if there's
something on my face first?
Nice comeback!
Oh, sorry about that.
I was just so happy to meet Alya-chan's friend.
Right...
Right, shall we get going?
Uh, what was that?
Oh, right, sorry. I said, "Shall we get going?"
Oh, sure.
See you later, President.
Yeah, take care of it.
How about this aromatic here?
I don't think that's
a good idea for the office.
That belongs more in your own room.
Gosh!
Look at this kitty plushie!
It looks just like Alya-chan!
I've got it!
How about getting a plushie that
resembles each student council officer?
Are you trying to build a theme park?
The girls may like it, but I bet it'll
make the prez uncomfortable as hell.
For him,
we'll get this bespectacled lion over here.
Listen, seriously...
Wait, that does look like him!
We'll get this, then.
Sure, it looks like him,
but I don't think plushies are gonna fly.
What...
Right back at you.
Fine.
But I'll get this kitty for myself. It's cute.
Better not get it on the same receipt.
Alya'll get mad at you. She's the treasurer.
Help. She's way too eccentric.
Is she always like this?
If she is, then Alya must've
gone through a lot.
This is the place, Kuze-kun.
Oh, okay. I'll hold that for you.
Thank you.
Take care of Alya-nyan for me.
A...
Alya-nyan?
My, you two look great together.
I have doubts about your tastes.
Say cheese.
Oh, no you don't.
Come on, what's the big deal?
Aren't we here to pick up tea?
Ugh, fine.
Here.
Thank you.
These leaves are first flush,
so they have a slight bitterness.
Say, Kuze-kun.
What do you think?
Uh, I'm not really an expert in red teas.
No?
Yuki could probably chime in.
That mother of ours has taught her a lot.
But I...
I'm sorry, Masachika.
Your mother and I have
decided to live separately.
Okay.
Then I'll follow...
I'll choose to go with you, Dad.
I'm sorry, Nii-sama.
I'm going to stay here.
Kuze-kun?
Is something wrong?
N-No, it's nothing.
You look terribly pained.
It's okay.
There, there.
What is this feeling?
It's so familiar... and so relaxing.
Ow! Hot!
Oh?
M-Masha-san! The tea's touching my back!
Oh, dear.
Ow!
Oh, dear!