Student Council Office
We're back.
Hey, welcome back. Thanks...
What's that thing you're holding?
Isn't it cute?
It certainly is,
but please don't tell me
you're going to keep it here.
May I?
I beg you, please reconsider.
Here are the supplies we got.
Let me see.
Okay, perfectly ordinary supplies.
You're a lifesaver, Kuze.
Who knows what the elder Kujo would've
done if left to her own devices?
The student council office
would've become a theme park.
Well, Kuze? Changed your mind
on joining the student council yet?
No, though I wouldn't mind
helping out occasionally.
Then why not join on paper?
I'm glad you agree with
bringing him on, Elder Kujo.
"On paper"? Come on now...
And I understand Yuki wanting me to join,
but why are you so set on bringing me on, Prez?
Why are you so set on not joining?
Something tells me there's more
to it than all the work involved.
I'm not worthy of being
a student council officer.
"Not worthy"? I can't say I agree.
After all, you were a fine vice president
for the middle school's student council.
That experience is what proved it to me.
I didn't have any suitable goals that I could
use that position of power to achieve.
And what's wrong with that?
Huh?
I became student council president
to win the heart of the girl I love.
A reason far more improper
than any you may have.
Wait, really?
Take a look at this.
Is that your younger brother?
That was me back in ninth grade.
Huh?
What?
Sometimes
in Russian
Hides Her
Feelings
Alya Sometimes Hides
Her Feelings in Russian
Episode 4
An Outpouring of Emotion
Surprised?
Y-Yeah.
Quite the transformation, I must say.
You could judge me by my cover two years ago.
My grades sucked, I was terrible at sports,
and I didn't like school very much, honestly.
But then I had to go and fall for
one of the two great beauties
in our grade, a girl way out of my league.
You mean your girlfriend?
Yeah, Sarashina Chisaki, the vice president.
I worked my butt off to become
a man worthy of being her boyfriend.
Becoming student council president
was part of that.
Pretty improper, see?
I guess so.
The point is, you don't need
a "suitable" reason.
Even Elder Kujo over there only joined
because Chisaki asked her to.
Was that it?
Yeah. Though I was interested in it before.
I think it doesn't matter why you join,
only what you do in your time here.
You can join for love or friendship
as long as you work to make
things better for the students.
Is that how it works?
That's how it should work.
Otherwise, only saints could ever
hold positions of power.
You make a good point.
There you have it.
Together with Suou,
you made things better as middle school
student council vice president.
Hold your head high. You have
absolutely nothing to be ashamed of.
Seirei Academy
Middle School
Student Council Election
Onii-chan, always be there for me, okay?
Don't wanna. Sounds like a pain.
What? But you're my brother!
If you want to join the student
council to make someone president,
that's perfectly fine.
Chisaki, Elder Kujo, and I
will welcome you with open arms.
We won't hear a word against it.
I'll think about it.
Sure, take all the time you need.
Such is the privilege of young'uns.
You say that like you're
not a "young'un" yourself.
Honestly, you don't
really look your age, though.
I get that a lot.
I was mistaken for a graduate student recently.
You do have this weird air of importance.
"To make someone president," huh?
Do I now?
Wait, where's Alya right now?
Oh, she's off mediating a dispute
between the baseball and soccer teams.
What dispute?
The baseball team has inter-school
matches every year around this time,
and they use the school field to prepare.
But the soccer team has entered
the regional qualifiers this year.
So they asked for permission
to use the school field instead.
And Alya's gone to mediate between the two?
Yeah. Neither team is backing down.
The baseball team has
pro scouts coming to observe.
That reminds me... The baseball team's
captain was featured on TV.
He's well-known around
these parts as the future of the team.
It's usually Chisaki in charge of
these inter-club disputes,
but she's away on important
kendo club business.
So I sent the younger Kujo, hoping it'd
serve as good experience for her,
but it sounds like she's having trouble.
Student Council Office
See you, then.
I'm just gonna go check
in case they're fighting.
Again, home advantage is very real in soccer.
Plan better, then.
We scheduled this months ago
because we have these matches every year.
It's basically just a stupid
friendly match, right?
Hell no!
Calm down, everybody.
Putting each other down
isn't going to solve anything.
You got a better idea, then?
How about using the riverside
park nearby to practice?
Huh? The riverside?
Hey, it has a baseball field. There you go.
Screw you! You know it has a soccer field, too!
We'd be in better shape
using the school field.
Well, the same goes for us.
Our futures are riding on this game!
Can you stop being selfish for one second?
Like, the soccer team
has way more members than you.
You'd have a much easier time
relocating to the riverside.
That's not our problem.
Calm down, please!
Quit running your mouths!
Nobody...
Can you guarantee this won't have
a negative effect on our future prospects?
None of them will listen to me.
I...
I really don't have
what it takes to influence people.
"If trusting people means I'll regret it later,
I'd much rather do things alone.
Nobody can keep up with me, anyway."
Saying that, I've looked down
on people, pushed them away,
and refused to ever reach out to them.
And I'm paying for it now.
Who would ever listen to a person like that?
Someone who can only talk down to
them about what is "right" and "wrong"?
I'm all alone.
I know that. I get it.
I chose this for myself.
But... still...
Help.
Somebody...
Please help me.
Heya!
Sorry to interrupt.
The student council sent me as backup.
I'm Kuze Masachika,
student council general affairs.
Our futures are riding on this game!
Soccer Team
Can you stop being selfish for one second?
Like, the soccer team has
way more members than you.
You'd have a much easier time
relocating to the riverside.
That's not our problem.
Calm down, please!
Quit running your mouths!
This ain't gonna work, Alya.
Both sides are too heated.
They should go away
and discuss this another time.
I feel bad for her, but it's good experience.
Hang in there, Alya.
Help.
Somebody...
Please help me.
This is why you're all alone. You say these
things in a language nobody understands.
Sure.
I've got you.
Kuze-kun?
Kuze? The one who was
vice president back in middle school?
The president gave me the gist of it.
The issue is who gets the field and
who has to practice riverside. Is that right?
Yeah, that's right.
Thank you.
How about this, then?
The baseball team will practice riverside,
given they have fewer members to move.
In exchange, the bigger soccer team
will send people
to help with the whole process.
To help? What the heck?
Why do we get booted to the riverside?
Yeah, why?
We're not having that!
Stay calm!
We've got too many people to move!
We can't do it!
We've got too much equipment!
Hey.
In that case, us managers
will go help out the baseball team.
Is that okay?
Huh? Yeah?
If that'll get us out of this mess.
I guess it'd be nice if the soccer
team's managers came to help.
Y-Yeah, it would.
Tch. You sure changed your tune quick.
They're letting us use the field.
It's the least we could do.
Yeah, I guess.
We're okay with those terms. What do you say?
That works.
Great. That's that.
Both teams, please come to the student
council with your formal requests tomorrow.
Uh... My bad.
For sticking my nose in there
and hurrying things along.
I made you look bad.
It's fine.
Why did you make that proposal?
It should've been clear that
the baseball team wouldn't agree to it.
It seemed to me like you knew
that manager would offer to help.
Oh? I'm impressed you realized.
Of course I would.
You were staring at her the whole time
the baseball team was complaining.
You see, that manager is dating
the baseball team's captain.
What?
You wouldn't know, huh?
The baseball team's star
and the pretty manager.
When news of their relationship got out,
it was all anyone could talk about.
Oh...
You know how the captain wasn't
saying a word during the whole thing?
He wanted to help his girlfriend,
but as captain, he had to
keep his priorities straight.
And it was awkward for her because she
knew the soccer team was asking for a lot.
So I knew that she would jump on that proposal.
It was a bridge over troubled water, then?
For the two of them, yeah.
But, hey, the baseball team gets some
cute girls helping them with practice.
The soccer team gets to use the school ground.
Those two get to have practice
dates across club lines.
Killing three birds with one stone.
Hmm? Prez?
Hey. Did you reach a conclusion?
Yeah.
Kuze-kun made it all happen.
Great. Good job hanging in there, Younger Kujo.
Did you plan all that?
Hmm? Not really, no.
Should've played dumb. That response
proves you knew exactly what I meant.
Oops. You got me there.
Well? Have you made up your mind?
Yeah, I have.
I, Kuze Masachika, will have the honor of
being a member of the student council.
Sweet. It's great to have you.
Come to the office right away, then.
I feel like I got played, and I don't like it.
But I guess it's time
I resigned myself to my fate.
Student Council Application Form
It's getting late, so fill out this form
and bring it in tomorrow.
So, what, was he gonna make me
fill it out on the spot if we had time?
Say...
What's up?
Are you really joining the student council?
Yeah.
Are you doing it to stand in the student
council presidential election with Suou-san?
What if I am?
What will you do?
Will you give up on being president?
No.
I will become student council president.
Even if it means going up against you,
I will never back down.
Figures.
You've always been driven
and unwavering like that.
Yeah?
Then I'll make you student council president.
Huh?
If it's what you want, I'll do everything
in my power to make you president.
I'll make sure you never stand alone again.
I'll be there with you and for you.
So...
Shut up and take my hand, Alya!
We're a team now, Alya.
Thank you.
я тебя люблю.
Wh-What's going on?
Come up here, Masachka!
Are you serious?
I still had it in me to feel this way?
Ow, oww!
Wh-What?!
Were you just thinking about some other girl?
H-How can you tell?
Yikes, this is bad! Very bad!
Flashing back to a girl in your past?
That's #2 on the list of things a rom-com MC
should never do in a confession scene!
#1: Ask her to repeat what she said.
Tell me.
Y-Yes?
You just finished telling me
you'd be there for me, right?
Huh? Y-Yes.
I did say that.
And in the very next moment,
you were thinking about Suou-san?
No, it wasn't Yuki.
Huh...
Whoa! That seriously hurts!
Kuze-kun!
Yes, ma'am?
If you want me to overlook this,
shut up and take my hand!
Nice slap.
Jerk.
Let's go home, yeah?
Yes, let's.
That's the first time a girl's ever slapped me.
I've gained more XP as a man.
Did you hit your head when you fell?
My brain's perfectly fine, okay?
Right. I forgot that "barely functioning"
is your brain's default state.
What a thing to say to someone
who was considered a child prodigy.
A prodigy? You?
Not buying it, huh?
Is your cheek okay? Do you need ice?
Nah, it's fine. I just don't feel anything
on the left side of my face.
That doesn't sound fine at all.
I was kidding, obviously.
It just stings a little.
Okay...
What's with the blank look?
That was only a cheek kiss.
Aren't those supposed to be cheek-to-cheek?
That's right.
Uh, but...
That felt like... Wait, which was it?
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Yeah, see you.
Huh?
Seriously, which one was it?
Alya!
Say what you did in Russian so I know!
я тебя люблю.
I love you.
Love?
Who, Kuze-kun? Who, me?
Nope! N-O-P-E!
No way! Not in a million years!
I don't love Kuze-kun or anything.
I just got caught up in the moment.
That's it.
Let's say, hypothetically,
just for argument's sake,
that I am in love with Kuze-kun.
Even then, I have something
more important right now:
becoming student council president.
I should be focusing on
living up to his expectations.
If I ignored that and
asked him out or something...
Huh? You love me?
Uh, sorry.
That's not what I meant
when I said I'd be there for you.
Don't get it wrong! It's not like
I love you or anything, okay?!
I'm back.
Welcome home, Masha.
Masha? Did something happen?
Huh? What do you mean?
I mean...
Something did happen! I met someone wonderful!
What?
Ta-da!
Alya-nyan!
A... Alya-nya... what?
See! Doesn't it look just like you?
How, exactly?!
The expression in its eyes?
I don't think a stuffed toy
can emote with its eyes.
Aww...
Oh, right, Alya-chan.
About Kuze-kun.
What about him?
I just thought he was a very sweet boy.
I can see why you would fall for him.
Again, I am not in love with him.
Really?
Knock it off.
Mhmm. Okay.
I see how it is.
You're cute when you hide your feelings.
Wha?
But you should hurry up
and tell him how you feel.
Not much you can do if somebody
takes him away from you.
Wh-What are you even talking about?
Ah, to be young and in love.
Seriously, what is with her?