I hear a student congress was held the other day,
with Masachika and the heiress of
Taniyama Industries participating.
Right.
She took you to the wire in your
middle school presidential election,
so I expected good things from her.
But it seems she left
in the middle of the debate?
She must have had her reasons.
Whatever her reasons, it has resulted
in Masachika's campaign gaining legitimacy.
Listen, no matter who you are up against,
you aren't allowed to lose.
I realize that, Grandfather.
You may not be as gifted as Masachika,
but you know that with great gifts
come great responsibilities.
Responsibilities he ran away from.
He was born with unrivaled talents
and into unmatched privilege,
but he threw it all away.
Losing to him, of all people,
is absolutely not an option.
Are we clear, Yuki?
Of course, Grandfather.
Yuki-san?
Is something the matter, Mother?
Are you and Masachika-san still as close as ever?
Yes, of course.
Good to hear.
Uh, what about him?
Nothing. Never mind me.
You have Chinese class now, don't you?
Yes, online.
Good luck with that.
Thank you.
Ayano.
Yes, Yuki-sama?
Let me hug you for a sec!
As you wish.
Okay, I'm all better now.
Are you done?
Yeah, thanks.
Man...
Tiddies truly are great.
Sometimes
in Russian
Hides Her
Feelings
Alya Sometimes Hides
Her Feelings in Russian
Episode 9
Rom-commy with a Chance of Hypnosis
Heya, Kuze.
You did amazing in student congress last week.
I thought Taniyama-san had it in the bag
after hearing her argument, but whew.
How much of that did you have planned out?
Hey, at least let me put my bag down.
Morning, Alya.
Yes, good morning.
Wow, business as usual, I see.
Alya, these guys wanna hear more
about your exploits last week.
Huh?
Go ahead and get the deets from her.
I must go. My gacha needs me.
Kujo-san, did you write your own speech?
Huh? Oh, yes, that was me.
Wow, I'm impressed.
You're a great orator too, huh?
Th-Thank you.
Was not asking questions part of your strategy?
Right. We'd decided not to.
What about Kuze taking over partway, then?
I wasn't expecting that, either.
I can't believe Taniyama
straight up ran away, though.
She was the one who started it, too.
Talk about pathetic.
Kuze-kun, a moment.
Hmm?
Okay?
Oh, right. We had student council
business to take care of.
Sorry, we'll pick this back up later.
Student Council Office
Well?
What's up?
Did Taniyama getting ridiculed
bother you so much?
I mean, she was just...
Yeah, you and I know why she did what she did.
But remember, we did nothing wrong.
We simply fought fair and square.
There's no need to let what people say
about her bother us, is there?
I get that.
But we didn't actually beat them.
They simply forfeited.
What's your plan, then?
Let's assume we help her save face.
That'll mean our student congress
victory goes to waste.
I know...
That's what I would say if I were
putting our interests first.
But who cares about that?
Huh?
What matters is what you want to do.
Well, I want to help Taniyama-san, obviously.
But that'd be...
Okay, gotcha. Then that's what we'll do.
What?
Are you sure?
Of course. No point letting this drag out.
We'll sort this mess out and head into
the closing ceremony with a clear conscience.
I'm sorry. I know this will
create more work for you.
Don't worry about it.
Like I said, I'm here for you.
Kuze-kun...
I sense a disturbance in the air.
Scoot in!
E-Easy for you to say!
Wow, a situation straight out of a rom-com.
As their junior, the right thing to do here
is to pretend I saw nothing.
Whoa, wait a second.
Is a rom-com scene starting over here too?
Welp, we got a problem.
In many different ways all at once!
All I can do now is divert
her attention elsewhere!
ELSEWHERE
How long are you gonna keep hiding,
Prez, Sarashina-senpai?
What?!
Sorry about that. We missed
our chance to announce our presence.
Yeah. We were just looking
for something we dropped on the floor.
Well, how about we pretend none of us
saw or heard anything here?
Y-Yeah, good idea. Let's go with that.
Word of the Week
"Thoughtfulness"
Glad we have an agreement.
Let's go, Alya.
Er, um... I...
I just remembered something I need to do!
Student Council Office
Say, Nonoa.
Did you see Phamel's newest collection?
Pretty cool, huh?
I dunno... Nothing really grabbed me.
Oh... Guess I'll pass too, then.
Ugh, normies! Not going
anywhere near them!
That aside, Nonoa.
Wanna come to my house party on Sunday?
But we have exams coming up.
We could also have a study sesh.
Uh...
Y'know, aren't you being kinda distant lately?
I'm just kidding!
Count me in for the party.
Yay!
What? I'll go if Nonoa's going.
D'you need something, Kuzecchi?
Uh, y-yeah, kinda.
Oh, can't talk about it here?
I'd prefer not to, yeah.
Okay.
Well?
I'm all ears if you wanna ask me out,
but that's not what you're here for, is it?
Nope.
Wait, you're all ears?
I mean, I'm single right now,
and I don't really mind you.
Uh, maybe go out
with someone you actually like.
I've never dated anyone I really liked.
Talk about a problematic statement.
Can you blame me? I don't get
all that love and romance stuff.
Far be it from me to meddle in your affairs,
but you should probably try
to avoid selling yourself short.
Sayacchi told me the exact same thing!
It came with a bonus slap, though.
Seriously?
Taniyama's the type to throw hands, huh?
Oh, uh, that was probably a one-off.
Anyway, how can I help you?
Right. You know how people
are talking shit about Taniyama?
I'm wondering if we can put a stop to it.
Oh? I didn't think it'd bother you.
Well, it bothers my partner.
Ah, I get it now.
That's so sweet of her.
So? Why come to me about it?
You do realize I'm the enemy, don't you?
"Enemy," huh?
I'm sure you noticed that
I had plants in the audience.
Of course I noticed.
I can't believe you'd risk destroying
your friendships like that.
Frankly, I'm not attached to
any of my friends other than Sayacchi.
I don't really care if I lose 'em.
Can I ask you something?
People like Taniyama,
with a fire burning within,
should be a total mystery to you.
Why're you so attached to her, then?
Oh, you've got it the wrong way around.
She intrigues me because she's such
a mystery, and that's why I want her around.
Is that how it works?
Surely you get how it feels to be drawn
to someone with a fire you don't possess.
Now, we're both miserable cynics attached
to our shining-rays-of-positivity partners.
Why don't we get our
miserable little scheme rolling?
I don't know if I would go that far, but okay.
My proposal is simple.
We spread a rumor giving a plausible
explanation to why Taniyama left that day.
To make it seem like she
didn't run away from a fight?
Are you sure?
It'll bring your victory into question.
That's fine by us.
Huh...
Well, she's my partner. It's my job
to clean up after her to begin with.
So yeah, we have a deal. See ya.
Y-Yeah.
You know what this reminds me of? That manga
scene where you summon your trusty spy
and say, "Follow 'em.
Make sure not to be spotted."
Ayano.
Yes, Masachika-sama?
Whoa! Why are you here?!
Huh? Because you summoned me?
Don't go ignoring me now, Brother.
Seriously, what are you two doing here?
Oh, we noticed you approaching
Lady Nonoa, an enemy.
So we hid behind the teacher's desk
to eavesdrop on you.
The damn desk again?
And? What's the real story?
We were pretending to have a secret meeting,
not knowing that an actual
secret meeting would take place here.
What is wrong with you two?
Kuze-kun? Are you here?
Oh?
Alya-san? You're not jumping
to conclusions, are you?
What do you mean? There's nothing wrong
with three childhood friends hanging out.
Well, enjoy yourselves.
A-Alya!
Bah! Leaving me out of the fun?
Bro...
You just know she went,
"I made lunch for Kuze-kun to repay him
for helping me in the debate. Where is he?"
and looked for you all over school,
only to be hit in the face with disappointment.
Quit fabricating the most cliched of setups!
It was a different boy last time.
Was it?
Well, he's my boyfriend now,
so I figured why not.
Quit selling yourself short!
You need to value yourself more!
She didn't have to get that mad.
You're finally back, Nonoa.
What was that all about?
Oh, he was asking about Sayacchi.
He wanted to know why
she skipped school today.
Taniyama's skipping today?
Feeling down over losing the debate?
Oh, nah. It's my fault.
Besides, she only left the debate
because she was mad at me.
H-Huh?
What do you mean?
She found out halfway through student congress
that I had plants in the audience.
Y'know how it goes.
Again, I really just happened
to run into Yuki and Ayano there.
Oh, yeah?
Not buying it, huh?
Please, you don't need to make excuses.
I'm glad you three
childhood friends are so close.
Oh, all that aside,
will you study with me after school today?
You? Study? What kind of sick joke is that?
Now that's just rude, plain and simple.
Um... Alya-san?
What?
Aren't you sitting a little close?
Is that a problem?
Not really, no.
I guess it's fine as long as nobody s...ees?!
My, I apologize. I should have knocked.
Sister of mine!
Are you preparing for exams?
If you don't mind, may we join you as well?
No.
Alya? You heard her. What do you say?
Sure. I don't see a reason to refuse.
Yeah?
Thank you kindly.
I'd prefer we were alone.
You cutie, you! Quit being so adorable!
All you've been doing is reading the solutions.
Is that really going to help you prepare?
Tearing my hair out over problems
I don't get is a waste of time.
Time better spent
getting the solutions into my head.
How will you learn to put theory
into practice like that?
Not to worry.
Masachika-kun's always been like that.
Right, Ayano?
That's right. This is how Masachika-sama
has always studied.
Ayano? Is there something you don't get?
Oh, no...
Actually, yes.
What is it?
No, I couldn't bother you with it.
Relax. I'm not gonna
mock you over it or anything.
Actually, I would prefer it if you berated me
and called me a useless waste of space.
Not happening.
Is that so...
Wait, why do you sound disappointed?
Are you three really just childhood friends?
Huh? Yeah, why?
I mean, you seem awfully close,
even for childhood friends.
Hi there, everyone.
Mm! Masha-senpai's tea is simply divine!
My, what is this?
Oh, Sarashina-senpai apparently
confiscated that book from someone.
Hypnosis for Dummies
Become a hypnotist today!
Kyoto Publishing
Huh...
Alya-chan, try it on me!
No way.
What? Why not?!
I wanna try getting hypnotized!
I wanna, I wanna!
Again, no.
Then you do it, Kuze-kun.
Huh? Why me?
I mean, Alya-chan's being a big old meanie.
Well, if you insist.
We start off with... hypnotic induction?
Hypnosis for Dummies
Become a hypnotist today!
Hype!
Uh... Okay, focus your eyes on my finger.
Your finger?
That's what it says.
Got it.
"You feel your mind slowly go into a trance.
Keep your eyes right here.
You're getting very, very sleepy.
When I clap my hands,
you will fall into a deep slumber."
Three, two, one... There.
Huh? Masha-san?
Masha-senpai? Did you really get hypnotized?
Yeah, yeah, very funny. Knock it off.
Masha?
U-Uh, let me undo the hypnosis.
Let's see...
"When I touch your shoulder,
you will snap out of it."
One...
Two, and there.
Um... Why did you stop, Kuze-kun?
What?
Come on! You said you would clap your hands!
Wait, what? Do you not remember?
Remember what?
Seriously, Masha, that's not funny.
Alya-san, why don't you have
Masachika-kun hypnotize you too, then?
Huh?
Wha?
You'll know whether she's telling
the truth or not one way or another.
I'm ready. Go ahead.
Are we seriously doing this?
Get on with it.
We're putting an end to this farce.
Fine. Focus your eyes on my finger.
Way too easy.
And why the heck did Masha-senpai
get hypnotized again?
Don't ask me.
For real? It's a booby-booty
grabby-grabby free-for-all!
Don't say the quiet part out loud!
Ready or not, it's time for otaku improv!
Improv
The topic: You just hypnotized two hotties!
What is the first suggestion you try?
Otaku
Mental age regression!
Make them totally unrestrained
and have them strip!
U-Uh... Make them reveal their deepest,
darkest secrets, maybe?
"Make them unrestrained"?
Couldn't you have been more specific?
Yeah, well, your answer was just depraved.
As for Ayano, not a bad answer,
but it's a bit lacking in impact.
Making them totally unrestrained
is the only right choice here.
They might even reveal their most
embarrassing secrets in that state.
Your answer even covered my suggestion?
You never cease to amaze.
There. I win by majority vote.
Alya-san, Masha-senpai, you two
will become more and more unrestrained.
Freed from the shackles of your inhibitions,
you will lay your minds and bodies bare.
Wait, what? For real?
Mm?
Huh?
Tell me, Yuki. Why am I getting
infinite head pats right now?
Good boy! Good girl!
G-Gee, I wonder why.
Look me in the eye, culprit.
I didn't expect Masha-senpai's
harem time to begin, not Masachika-kun's.
That's your problem?
Good boy, good girl.
Uh, Masha-san?
Could you let me go now?
What? Not happening.
Not happening, huh?
...oying.
Off with you.
A-Alya? What are you doing?
Office worker who's a superstar at work
but a slob at home, pictured in the morning!
Right?!
Whoa, what? Why'd they both
start taking off their clothes?!
Right, I did say they'd get more unrestrained
and lay their minds and bodies bare.
Er... When I touch your shoulder,
you will snap out of it!
One, two, and there!
Hey! That didn't work!
Uh... When I touch your shoulder,
you will snap out of it.
One, two, and there.
Yikes. This ain't working.
Are you serious?!
What are we gonna do about this?!
Masha? I got done a while a... go...
Uh, what's going on here?
S-Sarashina-senpai.
Well, you see...
I tried out what was written
in the hypnosis book,
Hypnosis for Dummies
Become a hypnotist today!
Kyoto Publishing
but now we can't snap them out of it.
Yeah?
Hup. Excuse me one moment.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! What?
What the hell was that?!
A reset.
What...
Huh? Why am I on the couch?
What?
Um, I can understand your confusion,
but you should probably get dressed first.
Huh?
Get dressed...?
H-How did this happen?!
No!
By the way, Kuze-kun.
You saw, didn't you?
Do you want a reset too?