Sometimes
in Russian
Hides Her
Feelings
Alya Sometimes Hides
Her Feelings in Russian
Episode 12
Chin Up and Face Forward
If you think I'm lacking something as
a president, feel free to point it out.
Thank you for your time.
Okay.
Now if you can do this at the closing
ceremony, we won't have a problem.
Right. I need to do this at the ceremony...
Worried?
You did fine during the student congress.
I only managed that because
I was focused on my own thoughts.
Besides, we'll have a bigger
audience tomorrow, won't we?
That's right.
This auditorium will be packed
with students tomorrow.
But it won't change what we have to do.
Just focus on delivering your message.
I don't think that's going to work.
I realized that while watching you talk
during the student congress.
How can I engage the audience like you do?
I really don't know how to answer that.
A lot of it comes down to experience.
Wanna know a little trick to break
the ice and grab the audience's attention?
A trick?
Yep.
Uh...
Simple, ain't it? And it works wonders.
Okay, I'll give it a try.
Rehearsing for tomorrow?
Yep. You done with your work?
Yes, of course.
What seems to be the matter, Masachika-kun?
You're wearing a rather foul expression.
Oh, playing dumb, are we?
You realize your mask
is starting to crack too, right?
You don't say.
See? This is what she's really like.
Don't be fooled.
R-Right.
Oh, Alya-san.
Are you perhaps disappointed in me?
Not at all. I have no reason to be.
It's only natural that people behave
differently in different circumstances.
And you meant it when you said you wished
to remain friends with me, didn't you?
Yes, I certainly did.
Then it's fine.
You gave me an opportunity
to take stock of myself.
And?
You asked me yesterday why I wanted
to be student council president.
I intend to give you my answer tomorrow.
Your forthright nature
really shines through, Alya-san.
It makes you a fascinating person.
Boy, I'm so glad that whole thing
didn't ruin your friendship with Alya.
Oh? You almost make it sound like it did
sour my friendship with you, however.
Not really?
I just think it was real classy of you.
Are you mad at me?
Far from it.
Attacking your opponent's vulnerabilities
is the clear and obvious move.
Just... How do I express how I'm feeling here?
I don't really understand it
myself, but it's kinda like...
I half want to give my pet dog
head pats for daring to bite me,
and half want to teach it a lesson
so that it never tries again.
Know what I mean?
You took a bite, so you'd better
sink those teeth all the way in.
Oh, there you are.
Heya.
Let's do a final rundown of tomorrow's plans.
That leaves the order of tomorrow's speeches.
How do you want to do this?
Last year, the candidates played
rock-paper-scissors to decide.
That sounds acceptable to me.
Not to me.
RPS rewards reading your opponent too much.
What?
You have a point.
How about a coin toss, then?
That's fair.
Very well.
How about Ayano does the coin toss,
and Alya-san guesses?
Nah, someone else should do the toss.
Not very trusting, are you?
Hey, want me to do it?
Please, Masha-san, if you would.
If Alya guesses right, we get first choice.
If she doesn't, Yuki will get to choose.
Masha... Are you sure you're up for this?
Hey! Don't mock your big sis!
I can do this.
Just watch.
Go!
If I go first and set the bar high enough,
I can score a decisive victory.
What if I go second?
The first pair will get polite applause
while the audience weighs its options.
It won't be an outright domination
if Alya-san gets to go first.
Should I take first dibs?
But it'd be smarter to go second
and see what Onii-chan does first.
Speaking of, why'd he try so hard
to intimidate me just now?
It's not like him.
He usually operates in the background.
There, I caught it!
See? I did it, Alya-chan!
You've made your point.
Heads.
Huh? Shouldn't you think about it some more?
It's fine. Get on with it.
Ugh.
Okay, here.
Oh, it's tails.
Yuki-chan, do you want to go first or second?
Well...
What if Onii-chan's outburst was all an act?
To what end?
Did he challenge me head-on in a bid
to distract me from something?
Alya-san!
Right. I got distracted by Onii-chan there,
but my target has been Alya-san all along.
She's surprisingly emotionally fragile.
Yesterday's broadcast
must be eating away at her.
And I was going to pile on the pressure
by making her go second!
Onii-chan's goal is to go first, get that
polite applause, and make it a draw.
In which case, I should stick to
the original plan and look to dominate.
I'd like to go first, please.
Okay, you got it.
The Suou-Kimishima pair will go first,
and the younger Kujo-Kuze pair will go second.
Got it.
Closing
Ceremony
As we look back on the first term,
I'm sure all of you have learned
a fair few lessons to take away.
Our aim is to continue to promote
self-discipline among the student body...
Next, we have the student
council's presentations.
Starting with the student council
president, Kenzaki Toya-san.
Hello, everyone. Good job
getting through the first term.
Two months have passed
since our student council has taken office.
Our numbers may have dwindled, but I truly
believe in the team we have put together.
Don't go slacking off
just 'cause it's summer break, guys.
Remember to plug away
at the homework and workouts every day.
It is important to take it one day at a time.
Maybe I should take a walk
to the park every day myself.
Speaking of walks,
let me tell you what happened...
Next, we'll hear from Suou Yuki-san.
Ready to roll, Ayano?
Yes, Yuki-sama.
A very good afternoon to everyone.
I'm Suou Yuki, student council spokesperson.
I will be a candidate in next year's
student council presidential election.
I look forward to working with you all.
Go for it!
You've got my vote!
Thank you kindly.
Now, in light of that, I would like
to share a part of my vision with you.
What I want to do when I become
student council president...
is to bring about an academy
that takes its students' opinions seriously.
Oh? Were you not expecting
something so ordinary from me?
Suggestions Box
I'm talking about this suggestions box,
to be more specific.
It has been available in our school for years,
but I believe most students
have never once made use of it.
I have addressed many of
the suggestions on my PA broadcasts,
but I've also found the box empty
most of the times I've checked.
Is that because you think writing in
is a waste of time and that nothing will get done?
Yeah...
That's right.
That's perfectly understandable.
Most council officers are busy dealing with
the challenges of their new posts.
With their hands full
just completing their tasks,
they find it difficult to divert
their attention to student needs.
However,
when I become president,
your wishes will be fulfilled!
For instance, you may want
the sports day competitions to be changed
or school festival events
to be altered or expanded.
Holding new events such as on Halloween
or Christmas might be fun too, don't you think?
As someone who was president
of the middle school student council
and is now an officer in high school,
I have the track record, the experience,
and the firm belief that I am uniquely
positioned to make all of this happen.
Thank you for your time.
Gah, that's dirty.
She talked a lot of bull and said
absolutely nothing of real substance.
But that was a masterful speech.
She's way better than I could ever be.
Are you okay, Alya-chan?
I'm fine. Just leave me alone right now.
Jeez, quit being so cold.
Who is that?
I don't remember seeing that beauty.
I am Kimishima Ayano,
student council general affairs.
Outside of school, I serve the Suou family
as Yuki-sama's personal attendant.
What's an attendant?
Dunno.
And I intend to stand for next year's
election as her running mate.
Yuki-sama is a person of extraordinary
talents and exemplary conduct.
And yet, she shows not a smidge of conceit.
Her capacity for empathy
and kindness is unmatched.
Hmph.
A safe, well-curated speech.
Her grades are always excellent.
Her English is native-level.
No wonder they went first.
They're trying to shut the door on us.
She's even begun studying Chinese recently.
You doing okay?
Yes.
Good.
She has shown herself to be gifted with
the piano, flower arrangement, and karate—
Do you remember
what this part of the event is called?
The student council officers'
greeting, right?
...truly an academic and an athletic prodigy.
Exactly. It's a greeting.
Let's present you to the audience
and let them get to know you.
I have no doubt that she will be a fine
leader and student council president.
Thank you for your time.
Next, we have Kujo Alisa-san,
the student council treasurer.
She was funny.
Kimishima-san, was it?
Suou-san knows how to pick 'em.
We basically have our next president already.
Right?
My apologies. I was so nervous, I seem to
have defaulted to speaking in Russian.
Was that... a joke?
I guess?
How does that even happen?
Listen up.
If we end up having to go second,
start your speech in Russian.
The crowd will still be buzzing about Yuki
and Ayano's speeches when you step up.
So pour cold water on them by
talking at the audience in Russian.
Let me start over. I am Kujo Alisa,
student council treasurer.
I intend to run for student council
president in next year's elections.
I only transferred into this academy last year,
and I have no track record to boast of.
I can't say I fully understand
what council work
and presidential responsibilities
entail just yet.
There is a lot I'm lacking as I am now,
and I'm aware of that.
However, there is one thing that
I can say with my head held high.
And that is...
I'm a person who can and does
work harder than anybody else.
I have always strived to bring what I believe
to be the ideal outcome to fruition.
That's because I believe that we as people
must never rest on our laurels
and must always try to better ourselves
and aim for greater heights.
I'll admit that my drive
has at times sown discord,
causing me to experience bitter failures.
But I learned from my mistakes
and helped my class win the best attraction
award at last year's middle school festival.
I didn't do it alone, of course.
I'm sure there's a lot I'm lacking in order
to be a fine student council president.
I know full well how driven
and how earnest and hardworking you are.
Chin up, Alya!
And yet I find myself here,
speaking to all of you...
in my own words, straight from my heart.
And I'm going to keep making up
for what I lack, one step at a time.
If I don't think I'm worthy of being
president by next year's elections,
I will take myself out of the race.
So I ask you, please keep an eye out
for who I am and what I do from now.
All of it will fuel me into becoming
the president you need, deserve, and want.
Thank you for your time.
Good job.
That was great.
You think?
Yeah. You were cool as hell.
I feel like I got over the hump.
Next up, we'll hear from Kuze Masachika-san.
Good luck.
I got this.
All right.
Time to go win.
Heya. I'm Kuze Masachika,
student council general affairs.
You may have heard that Suou Yuki had
a VP that pulled the strings behind the scenes.
That VP? Yours truly.
Huh?
Bro, that joke bombed hard!
Anyway, I think some of you might know
that I was once middle school vice president.
Which, naturally, would lead
to the following question:
"Wait, why aren't you running
with Suou-san, then?"
"Are you cheating on her now? Is that it?!"
Let me make this perfectly clear!
I dumped Yuki's sorry ass!
So this is not cheating!
Dude, you suck!
President hopping, much?
So, why did I dump Yuki
and decide to back Alya instead?
What kind of person do you all think is
most fit to be student council president?
A capable, responsible person?
One with mental fortitude?
I have to disagree.
I think the person most fit to be president
is one with the charisma
to draw people to them.
What did you all think of
Alya's speech just now?
I personally thought it was awkward as heck.
But, at the same time, I also felt
it was really genuine and heartfelt.
Alya's a straightforward person.
So much so that she used my idea
of starting her speech in Russian.
I chose to back her over Yuki because
I was drawn to that side of her
and wanted to support her in her pursuits.
And I would very much like
for all of you to do the same.
But one person's opinion
isn't going to be very convincing, is it?
So I'm going to tell you
something else—a fact.
When Alya becomes student council president,
Taniyama Sayaka and Miyamae Nonoa
will join her student council as officers.
Can you believe that?
Former debate rivals will be working together
in the same student council.
No way!
Yo, look.
Whoa, seriously?
That's all from me.
We ask for your support to bring
a brand-new kind of student council to reality.
Alya, you made this applause happen.
Now we're even.
Yes, thank you.
You were a great help.
I won't be helping your campaign any more.
I understand.
I'll do my best to earn your approval as well.
Don't let me down.
Good luck with everything.
If Alissa becomes president,
I'll be on your team.
A... Alissa?
This is why I want to become
student council president.
Your motivations won't overpower me anymore.
They got us.
My apologies.
If only I had delivered a better speech...
It isn't your fault, Ayano.
I made the wrong call in trying
to win with strategy alone.
I suppose I should admit defeat for today.
Just for today.
Yuki-sama.
Hmm?
You're giving off amazing boss vibes right now.
Uh, I wasn't trying to.
SUMMER BREAK!!!
Now, if I'd hit my goal,
it would've been the icing on the cake.
Term 1 Finals Ranking
1st - Kujo Alisa
2nd - Suou Yuki
Tell me about it.
33rd
\
Kuze Masachika
Talk about anticlimactic.
I guess there are things
even this prodigy can't do.
Says you?
So, any complaints about this outcome?
None!
All good, then. Let's head home.
Today was a lot. I'm kind of worn out.
Yeah, sounds good.
Hey, Alya?
What?
Y'know, what about our bet?
I have to do one thing you ask for, right?
I'll come up with something.
Didn't you have something in mind already?
You gave me a hint in Russian.
Oh, that... I was just saying whatever.
What the heck? I assumed you were going...
Oh, she wasn't counting
on winning the bet, huh?
Er, what was it? I think she said
"given name" or something?
Uh...
Alya?
Well, we've now made
our address to the student body
and been recognized
as running mates for the election.
Why don't you start calling me by my given name
to show off that we're a close-knit team?
I guess that's a decent idea.
O-Oh, yeah?
Y-Yeah?
Well, in that case...
Masachika...kun?
Y-Yeah... N-Not too bad, I'd say.
Y-You think?
Let's go with that, then.
Y-Yeah.
Whoa! Better switch to our outdoor shoes!
R-Right!
Alya.
Uh...
It may be summer break,
but we still need to prep for the election.
Yuki and Ayano are gonna be
together the entire time.
So, you know...
What do you say we meet up
over the break, too?
Masachika-kun.
Hmm?
Face forward.
Gladly!