Yikes, what was I thinking?
"I'll be there for you," my ass.
"Shut up and take my hand," my foot!
Gah, that was so corny!
Alya totally said "I love you"...
Does that mean she was seriously
flirting in Russian all this time
and not just playing a solo game
of chicken going, "Does he know?"
But tonight came from the heart...
Yeah, right!
She must've gotten caught up
in the moment like I did.
She's probably come back
down to earth and cringing hard by now.
Yeah, that must be it.
You have to work again?
You're never home these days!
Why do you always have to be like this?
Do you think apologizing
magically makes it okay?!
Love is a flimsy and unreliable emotion.
Racking my brain over it is a waste of time.
I'll be there for her?
Who, me? The guy who ran away and left
Yuki to carry on the Suou family name alone?
Ridiculous.
Didn't she say she was busy today?
Wait.
If today's events were all carefully laid out
to get me to join the student council,
then of course Yuki would be in on it.
Sometimes
in Russian
Hides Her
Feelings
Alya Sometimes Hides
Her Feelings in Russian
Episode 5
Different People, Common Undercurrent
Eek! Onii-chan, you perv!
You little twerp. You set this up, didn't you?
You realized, huh?
Of course I would.
I bet you got out when you heard me
closing the front door.
Not so fast, now.
Aren't you curious about why I did this?
We can talk after you put on your clothes.
Hear me out first, Masachika-kun.
I realized something crazy a few moments ago.
And what was it?
You see, we lived together for years,
but we never cleared the
"walking in on her changing" cutscene!
I expected dumb, but this is the dumbest!
All brothers walk in on their sisters
changing at least once in their lives!
Maybe in 2D! Calm your otaku brain!
I am not taking that from you!
Anyway, fan service shot! Squee!
What are you even looking at?
A camera that a dumbass like you can't see.
But you can, with your whole ass out?!
Anyway.
All jokes aside, this is my way of
making it up to you for tricking you today.
What makes you think showing
your naked body will make it up to me?
Whoa, easy there, fella.
You're talking a big game,
but I know you checked me out
from top to bottom, aight?
Yuki.
I'm going to let you in on a big secret.
A showoff is a turn-off.
Sneak peeks are where it's at.
Ah. You've shown me the light.
Yeap.
Hold it right there. You're not fooling anyone.
You looked, didn't ya?
You looked me up and down, didn't ya?
Only down to the chest.
Your Honor! This boob goblin just admitted it!
Shut it, you flasher!
By the way, bro.
What?
And why are you drying your hair
in my bedroom like you own the place?
Did Prez and Masha-senpai manage to
talk you into joining the student council?
Yeah, but there's a catch.
I've decided to push for Alya
to be student council president.
O...
Oh, no! Alya-san cucked me
and took my Onii-chan!
There was no cucking involved!
Damn you, you booba baboon!
Were my C-cups not enough to satisfy you?
You had to get bewitched by
Alya-san's E-cups (citation needed)?
Shut up about cup sizes! Too graphic!
You need to open your eyes, bra.
I mean, bro.
You know Cs that are okay to touch
are better than Es you can't!
Uh, I'm pretty sure neither are okay!
Come at me, bro! But be gentle!
Why do you sound so excited?!
What will it be? Will you
take your sister's first boob grab?
Shut your mouth.
Just kidding. You already took it
back in elementary.
I don't recall that.
Huh?
Huh? Seriously?
Onii-chan...
Did you forget?
That was back when I was in second grade.
We crashed into each other
during a game of tag,
and you dove into my thighs and
grabbed a handful of my right boob!
I sure as hell would remember it
if I caused that kind of miracle!
Quit fabricating the most cliched
of perving moments!
Tch.
Did you just "tch" at me?!
Yeesh. You could barely ever go out
back then due to how bad your asthma was.
And look how well I am now!
I haven't even caught a cold
since middle school!
I'd prefer it if you curbed
your energy a little bit, honestly.
I do! At home and in school!
Uh, sorry.
Don't be sorry! Spoil me instead!
All yours.
Ah... So you've decided to run with Alya-san.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Huh? It's nothing to apologize about.
A sibling rivalry? Now that's classic.
Just so we're clear,
I'm not sick of you or anything, okay?
I know.
I mean, you love me to death, right?
I guess.
Heh, you admitted it.
Shut it.
Okay, I'm good now.
Yeah?
Yeah, thanks.
Anyway, I guess we're rivals now.
Oh, right.
I'm an easy girl. I can overlook
a cheating episode or two.
So you can come back to me
anytime if you get tired of Alya-san.
Uh, quit calling it cheating.
And no, I'm not gonna do that.
Please. Quit acting like you're not gonna
come home to me at the end of the day.
What are you, The One?
Later.
Buh-bye!
Oh, so he found someone
who could motivate him.
Aww, sucks that I couldn't be the one to do it.
Not that it matters.
I'm still not gonna lose.
It's unusual that she didn't come
make a huge scene to wake me up.
I guess she was hurt by my decision deep down.
Yeah, no. Not her.
But I'd better try to make it up to her anyway.
If you thought this was gonna
end all sappy-like, think again!
I said I would do this,
and I always walk the talk!
Why, you little...
Huh?
Pull me out.
What?
I'm stuck.
Don't make me spell it out.
Wh-What are you doing?!
I'm gonna bury you alive, you punk!
To your grave!
This reeks of boy! It's gonna knock me up!
Like hell it will! What are you,
some kind of sheltered princess?!
I literally am though! Problem?!
Morning!
Did you catch the show last night?
Yeah, that was so good!
Right? It got me all warm and fuzzy!
What am I fretting about?
I bet he's going to walk in
with a sleepy face like always.
Just play it cool and act normal.
Hey there, Masachika.
Morning, Masachika.
Hey, morning.
Morning, Alya.
Good morning... Kuze-kun?
You prepping for class?
Y-Yes, I am.
What's the matter?
Huh? Nothing?
Yeah?
Masachika, Takeshi and I were talking.
We should go to karaoke sometime.
Sounds good. When?
He's not his usual self today.
Sometime this week?
Alya
POV
He seems somewhat fragile...
And it's kind of hot!
Wait, what am I thinking?
He probably just didn't get
enough sleep like always.
He's not dozing off. Why?
Is he seriously stepping up his game for me?
I'll be there with you and for you.
Kujo-san!
Team
Awesome!
So good!
That was insane!
Kuze!
Hey, you okay?
He's out cold!
"The ball is my best friend"?
You lied to me, Tsubasa.
I'm starved.
Kuze-kun, are you okay?
Alya?
What's up?
I was worried you might be hurt.
You saw that, huh?
Are you okay? Want to go to the nurse's office?
I'm fine. I just stepped outside
because it's too hot in the gym.
I'll go back in after a little break.
Really?
Let me see.
This doesn't really tell me much.
Y-Yeah?
E-cups... Is it true?
Wait. She said "citation needed."
They might be even bigger!
Yo, what? A peek at the pits?!
Is she doing this on purpose?!
You see now, Yuki?
Sneak peeks really are where it's at.
What?
Uh, nothing!
Anyway...
You should drink some water.
Huh? R-Right.
Oh...
Huh? Kuze-kun?!
Wh-What are you doing?
Uh...
Just thought I should cool my head. Literally.
O-Oh.
My, if it isn't Kuze-kun.
What's this? A man dripping with
charisma from head to toe, are we?
Hey there, Masha-san.
I was just cooling off. Nothing to worry about.
What's up? Do you see something in the sky?
I see clouds.
As do I.
Thank you, Captain Obvious.
I have gained a new appreciation
for gym uniforms.
You're soaked. Do you have a towel?
Nah. I'll just let the sun do its job.
Okay, bend down for me.
Wh-What's going on?
I've never encountered
a scene like this in any media!
There.
All done.
Well? Feel better?
I do. And now I get how a dog feels.
What kind? An Akita?
Uh, don't ask me about the breed.
Sorry for being a rowdy mutt.
A naughty dog has its charms, you know.
Come on.
We're going back, Kuze-kun.
You should get back to class too, Masha.
Wha... I just got here.
Too bad. We're heading back.
Fine.
See you after school.
Yeah, see you.
Thanks for the towel.
Okay, I see where this is going.
She's gonna call me "creepy"
or "dirty" or something.
So, are you okay now?
Huh?
I mean your head. Are you okay
not icing the part where the ball hit you?
Oh!
She thinks I doused myself to cool off
the part where the ball hit me!
Oh, yeah, I'm good.
I don't have a lump or anything.
Really?
No, really, I'm fine!
What's going on?
Why is she being so nice to me?
Has she entered her lovey-dovey phase?
Uh, Alya-san?
Aren't you being awfully nice to me today?
I mean...
You haven't been yourself all day.
I'm a little worried something's wrong, is all.
Hmm?
Oh... Ah.
I guess I wasn't fully over letting Yuki down.
Nah, nothing's wrong...
It's just, I skipped breakfast this morning.
Wha?!
Here I thought you were
paying attention in class for once,
but you were simply
too hungry to fall asleep, huh?
No. That was because
I got a good night's sleep.
Huh... Oh?
A good night's sleep, eh?
I had so much trouble sleeping
after what happened last night.
But this carefree clown ignored
all that and snored it up all night, did he?
So that's how it is.
H-Hear me out, Alya.
You know what the Lord has said?
What, are you going to remind me
to love my neighbor?
Nah. The Lord has said,
"If anyone slaps you on the right cheek,
turn to them the other cheek also."
Is that a look of scorn
toward a masochistic pig I see?
No, it's a look of scorn
toward a goofy good-for-nothing.
Forget it! I was a fool for worrying about you!
What a jerk!
There's no way I'm in love with this fool!
Great, there's the Alya I know.
Alya-san? Can we go to
the student council office together?
I may have crossed the line.
Pardon us!
Hey, it's those guys from
the baseball and soccer teams.
Excuse us.
Huh?
Sorry, wrong room.
Sorry about that.
I thought the guys from the baseball
and soccer teams came back for something.
Right...
Er, what did they do?
My dear junior went to mediate their dispute.
But they ignored her
and had a pathetic shouting match, I heard.
So I knocked some—
I mean, talked some sense into them.
I get it now.
I feel like bringing out your bamboo sword
may have been taking it too far, though.
I-It's fine.
My fists can be lethal,
but a bamboo sword's never killed anybody!
You don't say.
The sword will break before it does.
Sarashina-senpai. Well...
I've heard the boys call her "boss" before,
and now I see why.
Toya!
Relax a little, Kuze.
Chisaki didn't do any violence.
She simply used the threat of
violence to get them to behave.
Hey, Toya?!
Jeez, you jerk!
My bad.
Gee, what an adorable sight.
Why, you...
You... you!
Chisaki? You're gonna dislocate my shoulder.
Jerk! Jerk! Jerk!
But is it really, though?
Sorry, am I late?
Oh, my.
Don't play around too much in the office, okay?
Th-That's not what we were doing!
S-Sorry. Did that hurt?
Hmm? Oh, don't worry.
You happened to magically
fix my recent stiff shoulders.
I'm really sorry.
I can't control my power too well.
We've got one of warrior blood among us.
Relax. I've been building my body to handle it.
Come at me all you want.
Toya...
Huh? What about that was romantic?
Watch your mouth, will you?
Say, you know how the boys
call Sarashina-senpai "boss"?
Do you think she wears a sash in there?
Why would you think that?
I just figured that if she did,
that'd make it a Sash in a Sarashina-senpai.
Wow, aren't you two close?
How so?
Hmph. It seems your sister has seen through us.
And how close we are.
Eww.
Excuse me.
I apologize for being late.
Don't worry about it, Suou.
Let's begin the student council meeting, then.
Let's do this.
Okay, Kuze. Could you introduce yourself?
Sure.
I'm Kuze Masachika, and I'll be handling
general affairs for the student council.
Next year, Kujo Alisa here and I...
will be running mates
in the presidential election.
I look forward to working with you all.