Student Council Office
I'm an avid consumer of otaku media.
You can talk to me about most of
the popular anime or manga out there.
That's all.
Thank you.
That makes you an official member
of the student council.
For today, could you shadow
the elder Kujo and help her out?
Sure.
Thanks for that.
While I'm sure you'll adapt in no time
thanks to your experience as vice president,
I want you to work with the other
members while you learn the ropes.
Are we short-staffed or something?
Yeah, disastrously so.
I apologize for interrupting...
But I think I'll head over to the art club
to discuss their upcoming exhibit.
Yeah, take care of that.
I will.
Related to that,
I'm sure we'll end up discussing the budget,
so I'd like to ask Alisa-san,
the treasurer, to accompany me.
Huh?
I understand.
I'll be gone for a bit, President.
Sure. Go crunch those numbers.
Something's about to go down.
Sometimes
in Russian
Hides Her
Feelings
Alya Sometimes Hides
Her Feelings in Russian
Episode 6
A Kiss of the Indirect Variety
I feel like I should
bring it up myself.
Suou-san.
Do you have a moment to talk?
Of course.
Instead of doing it here,
why don't we use
that empty classroom for a bit?
I'm going to run for president
together with Kuze-kun.
Yes, I'm aware.
Masachika-kun told me as much last night.
He did?
Er, is that all?
That is all. I have no intention of
apologizing, because I did nothing wrong.
I simply wanted to give you the news in person.
Is that so?
Indeed, you have nothing to apologize for.
Masachika-kun chose this for himself.
I have no say in this decision,
nor do I have any intention
of taking any displeasure out on you.
However, I do find it regrettable
that he didn't choose me.
Suou-san, do you...
Nothing. Never mind.
Yes, I love him.
More than anyone in this whole wide world.
R-Really?
Really.
I love Masachika-kun more than
I do Mother and Father, even.
What about you?
How do you feel about Masachika-kun?
M-Me?
Kuze-kun's my friend.
A-And a very dear one, at that.
Do you like him?
Well? Are you in love with him?
I'm... not talking about that sort of thing.
Well, I just told you how much I love him.
Now it's your turn.
Make yourself clear.
I can't say if I'm in love with him or not,
but I won't let you have him.
He's mine!
Is that so?
I'm satisfied with getting
that much out of you today.
Let's head on over to the art club.
Y-Yeah.
Oh, right, while we're here...
If you don't mind, may I call you Alya-san?
Hearing Masha-senpai
and Masachika-kun call you that
made me want to use
that lovely nickname as well.
I don't particularly mind.
In return, please call me Yuki.
Yuki... san.
I appreciate it.
I...
I feel like I said something crazy back there.
Masha-san, can you check this part?
Oh, that's an error.
Yeah, I thought so. I'll fix it.
Please do.
Much to my surprise,
she's like a well-oiled machine at work.
On the other hand...
Huh? Where did I see this?
What? Why?!
Uh, Chisaki?
I hear they're doing a large-scale
restock over at the library,
and they're looking for people to help.
I got it!
Sorry about this, Kuze.
Chisaki is more or less always like that.
Still, she's a force to be reckoned with
in club and committee discussions.
I mean, everybody's got
their strengths and weaknesses.
Let's take a quick break, shall we?
I'll make some tea.
Oh, I'll help.
No, it's fine.
Have a seat and wait.
I like making tea.
Are you a milk tea person, Kuze-kun?
How about sugar?
Oh, we have jam too.
Jam? Like in Russian tea?
I'll take jam, then.
Sure thing.
And I assume you're okay
with protein powder, President?
Nothing okay about that.
I didn't expect that kind
of joke from you, Masha-san.
Actually, wait.
Isn't black tea more of
a winter drink in Russia?
Hmm, it depends on the household.
We drank tea all year round
when we were there, at least.
Partly because my mother
can't live without her tea.
She's Japanese, right? That makes sense.
Do you know a lot about Russia?
Not really, but I did watch some
Russian movies with my grandfather.
Oh, wow.
Well, that was just my gateway.
In all honesty, I studied like crazy
because I wanted to talk to that girl.
Here you are. Enjoy.
Thank you.
This is great.
You think so? Thanks.
This reminds me...
That mother of mine's
quite the tea aficionado herself.
Oh, so the jam doesn't always go in the tea?
It's personal preference.
Huh...
So sweet.
I'm back.
So am I.
Welcome back.
Would you two like some tea too?
Oh, gladly.
Give me.
Sure. Give me a second.
What?
Personal space? Hello?
In Russia, it's considered bad luck for
a young lady to sit at the corner of the table.
Is it?
It is.
Bit too close for comfort, though!
Wait, what? Did something really go down?
Uh, Masha-san?
Is what Alya said true?
Is there really a superstition like that?
There is.
They say unmarried people who take
the corner seat will never get married.
Did you find someone
you would like to marry, Alya-chan?
Of course not.
I just didn't feel like sitting there.
What? Really?
Drop it.
Marriage isn't in the cards just yet.
Yeah, we're only 15, after all.
Though something about
that phrasing's bugging me...
Wait, you're doing this
even with your sister around?!
Here, Alya-chan.
Help yourself while you wait.
What?
Nothing at all.
All right, let's call it a day.
Us second-years have something
to discuss with the teachers.
The first-years may leave.
Good work today.
Goodbye.
Okay, Yuki definitely did something
she shouldn't have.
Hey, Alya?
What is it?
Can we stop by here for a bit?
Huh?
Why?
We need to talk about some stuff
regarding the presidential election.
Oh...
Sure, why not?
Okay, let's head in.
So this isn't a date.
Is that what you were hoping for, Alya-san?!
What?
I didn't say anything.
I'm a bit worn out.
I need some sugar to get
my brain working again.
That so?
Uh... did something happen with Yuki?
Nuh-uh.
Yuki! What the heck did you do?!
Are you and Yuki-san dating?
Hell nah.
You're not?
Nope. Absolutely not.
But she said...
I'm only saying this cause you need to hear it.
She's not the prim-and-proper
lady she appears to be.
She's messing with you
and having fun seeing how you react.
Anyway...
Moving on to the election talk.
Let's get one thing out of the way.
We stand zero chance
of beating Yuki as things stand.
Not beating around the bush, are we?
It's the truth. That's how big
a front-runner Yuki is.
Normally, you'd have three pairs of aspiring
candidates in the student council at this time.
In fact, at the start of middle school,
our council had six pairs—
Yuki and me included—
meaning 12 aspirants in total.
That's so many.
That said, half of them dropped out at
the student congress right before the election.
Student congress?
It's something of a debate contest
held between students.
If, say, the dispute between the baseball and
soccer teams hadn't reached a compromise,
they would've had to debate each other
at the student congress to decide who won.
So that's what the events
I saw happening in the auditorium were.
Anyway, what do you mean,
half of them dropped out?
When the congress features
presidential candidates,
it essentially becomes a
preview of the election.
Once they debate on policy
and one side beats out the other,
it establishes a clear pecking order
in the eyes of most students.
I see what you mean.
Traditionally, the candidates fight each other
until the field gets whittled down
to three pairs or so.
Of course, not every candidate
joins the student council,
but the lack of numbers this year
is clearly abnormal.
Everyone's given up on beating Yuki.
What's with him?
He's acting like this doesn't bother him.
It goes to show that everyone thinks
she's a shoo-in as the next president.
Does he just not think anything of
coming to a restaurant with a girl?
The benefits of being student council
president at our academy go without saying.
In fact, that title is of such great value
No wonder I had such a hard time drinking with it. When did I do this?
that the elections were rife with
underhanded tactics until a few years ago.
But hey, thanks to all that,
now we get to have clean elections.
You listening to me, Alya?
I am. I was just momentarily
distracted by my parfait.
I mean, it definitely looks great.
Get off my case!
I'm only acting up because
of the way you're acting!
Fine, I got it.
If you're not going to get in the mood,
I'll get you in the mood myself!
Say, do you want a bite?
Nah, I'm good.
You said it looks great, didn't you?
No need to be shy.
Here you go.
Uh, I can just get a fresh spoon.
You'd call the staff over just for that?
It'd add to their washing load, too.
But...
Hurry up!
This is perfectly commonplace in Russia!
Wait, really?
Nope, she's totally lying.
Come on! Say "aah"!
She even said the magic words!
Guh! An indirect kiss, also featuring tongue!
Wow, that's sweet.
Yeah?
Is that Taniyama?
So, how do we beat Yuki-san?
Facing her head-on isn't gonna help.
We need to run a campaign that appeals
to students from a different angle.
Like how, exactly?
Take President Kenzaki, for example.
One of the candidates in last year's election
was a former middle school president.
And yet, it was President Kenzaki
who came out on top.
He wasn't on the council
in middle school, was he?
Nope, but he still won,
thanks to an elaborate strategy.
What was it?
Seirei Express
Kenzaki Toya's Path to
Student Council President
Volume 5:
The Return of the Abs
The newspaper club profiled him
because they were amused by him running.
I'm sure they were mostly
messing with him at the start,
but as the coverage went on,
his appearance changed, and his grades went up.
People were watching
a success story unfold in real time,
and they started rooting for him.
And that wave of support
carried him all the way to victory.
So you're saying I need a backstory
to rally support?
To show all the students
how hard I'm working and all that?
Always quick to catch on, I see.
But uh...
Whatcha gonna do with that spoon?
What do I do with this spoon?
Hey, uh, mind if I order something?
Huh? Feel free.
Here's your order.
And the fresh spoon you asked for.
Please enjoy.
You didn't have to.
Trust me, I had to do it for myself.
Getting flustered over something so minor?
You're a bigger baby than I thought.
And here I figured
you were used to female company.
Meanwhile, I'm over here
shocked by how casual you were about it.
What, is Russia rife with
indirect kisses or something?
You're the only one I would do that with, dummy.
Heh. Thanks.
Hurry up and eat that. It's gonna melt away.
You're right.
Anyway, how exactly do I
build support like President Kenzaki did?
Hmm, well, you'd need to show everyone
just how hard you're willing to work.
Our first chance is
the first term's closing ceremony.
Do you mean the student council address?
Yeah.
It's essentially the first policy speech
made to the whole student body.
I'm sure you realize how important that is.
What should I say in my speech?
Whatever you like.
The audience is more likely to be
receptive if you speak your mind.
What, do you not have
any specific advice to give?
You don't need to fake anything.
You're a perfectly captivating
human being as you are.
Oh, yeah?
How exactly?
Praise me more.
This is exactly what I mean, you charmer, you!
I thought they'd play it safer
since they're a casual diner.
Is that any good?
Yeah, kinda.
Wanna try?
Wait, Alya can't handle this level of heat.
That looks hot.
But if I back out, he'll realize
I'm not a fan of spicy food.
I'll have just a bite, then.
Y-Yeah, go for it.
A WHOLE
CHILI
Let her have it, bro.
Be honest. Seeing Alya-san
teary-eyed is such a turn-on, right?
No, don't bully Alya-chan like that.
Bad boy!
Get lost!
Forgive me, Alya.
Here you go. The best part.
Th-Thank you.
Alya?
You jerk!
You okay?
What do you mean? I'm fine.
If you say so.
Oh, yeah. What's Yuki-san going to do?
Huh?
I mean, if you're running with me,
that means she'll have to find
a new partn—running mate.
Well, she's absurdly popular on her own,
so I don't think it really matters...
But it'd have to be someone
who was on our student council, huh?
Yeah, we're in trouble if she
brings out the likes of Taniyama.
Who's Taniyama?
Taniyama Sayaka.
Back in middle school, she took Yuki
to the wire in the election we won.
Never heard of her?
Can't say I have.
Did she give up on ever becoming president?
Kuze-kun?
Oh, uh...
Well, I'm sure we'll find out who Yuki's
gonna team up with soon enough.
Seirei
Private
Academy
Student Council Office
I'd like to introduce you all to someone.
Ayano.
Kuze-kun?
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Kimishima Ayano from Class 1-C.
I'll be joining the student council
and handling general affairs.
I look forward to working with you all.
Masachika-sama, let's do our best
together as the general affairs team.
Ayano...