Masachika-sama.
Ayano...
You need something?
I apologize for startling you.
May I have a moment of your time?
Uh, okay.
Thank you.
Please follow me.
She's like a ninja. Never fails to amaze me.
Sometimes
in Russian
Hides Her
Feelings
Alya Sometimes Hides
Her Feelings in Russian
Episode 7
Thank you for taking the time to—
A Storm Arrives
Skip the formalities.
Get to the point.
My apologies.
Very well.
I hear that you're planning to run with
Kujo-sama in the presidential election.
Is this true?
Yeah.
Master has expressed
his displeasure with this turn of events.
He was incredulous that you stand in
Yuki-sama's way after abandoning the Suou name.
That geezer...
He gave me the whole, "If you leave,
we will be no more than strangers"
and "You will not be allowed to
call yourself Yuki's brother" spiel,
and now he wants to act like we're family?
Screw you, you dinosaur.
And?
He sent you to confirm whether it was true?
No, I'm asking of my own accord.
As Yuki-sama's aide, it is my job
to assess any and all threats to her.
Wow, such fealty. What are you, a samurai?
I... truly believed that you would never
do anything to cause Yuki-sama grief.
Was my trust in you misplaced?
I didn't decide to run in order to oppose Yuki.
It was just an unfortunate consequence.
Whatever your thought process,
the fact remains that you are now
on a collision course.
Is running with Kujo-sama so important to you
that you would betray
and hurt Yuki-sama to do it?
Yeah.
I promised her that I would do everything
in my power to make her president.
Is that because you harbor
special feelings for her?
Do you, perhaps...
Nope.
It was just something I decided I wanted to do.
So tell Gramps this for me:
Don't pester Yuki about this.
If you've got a problem,
come say it to my face.
Understood.
May I ask you one last thing?
Can I trust that your love
for Yuki-sama remains the same?
Yuki is still the most important
person in the world to me.
That part hasn't changed.
So, please, be there for her.
I understand.
I'm glad to have been able to hear
your thoughts on this matter.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
I guess I ended up disappointing her.
Young Blahblah
Ta-da! Check out this week's bikini cover!
Say, Masachika, who's your fave?
Sorry, I don't really get idols.
Dude, quit sounding like an old man.
Come on, you can pick off looks.
Well, in that case...
In this group, I guess that one?
Hmm?
The girl you picked kinda
looks like Kujo-senpai.
Oh?
Does she?
Now that you mention it, I see the resemblance.
Are you into girls like Kujo-senpai, Masachika?
Not really?
Masha-san has a boyfriend, anyway.
So you totally would if she didn't.
Wait, when'd you start using her nickname?
You been making a move, huh?
No way. It just happened.
I've never looked at her in that way...
You animal.
Do you really think it's okay for a student
council officer to bring that to school?
Well, actually, Takeshi was
the one who brought it.
Then you should tell him off.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, change of topics.
Ever thought about dating Suou-san?
Never. Not in a million years.
Why not?
I mean...
Anyway, I want a girlfriend
who can also be my best friend.
So, someone like me?
Masachika? What's wrong?
Uh, nothing.
And, well, I'd like a girl
with a cute smile.
Yeah, people with cold eyes
can feel quite distant.
How they carry themselves
in daily life really matters.
Hey, watch what you're saying!
You're hurting Alya!
Whatever.
It doesn't matter. I have friends.
Just gas her up some for now!
Okay, fine.
But, hey, that stuff doesn't matter when
we're talking about a girl as pretty as Alya!
You're not helping!
Huh?
Huh... So that's how you see me.
Well, excuse me for being a girl
who's all looks and no charm.
Uh, nobody said that.
Eek!
On second thought, I'm taking this.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Well? Satisfied now?
Yes. Masachika-sama
is still the man I idolized.
Glad to hear it. What'd he say?
He refused to back down
on running with Kujo-sama.
Figures.
He also asked me to tell Master, "If you've
got a problem, come say it to my face."
Hoo boy.
Them's fighting words.
Onii-chan's serious about this.
He is. His fantastic aggressiveness
sent shockwaves through my womb.
Uh-huh? It did that, huh?
Yes.
Uh... Just checking, you're not in love
with him or anything, are you?
That is correct.
I idolize him as I do you, but there are
no romantic feelings involved.
Is that so...?
I would never have the gall
to seek to be his girlfriend.
All I wish is to serve him well as a tool.
Way to sound like a sub!
I'm afraid I don't understand.
What do you mean by "sub"?
Huh? Er... A super maid Serving Under a Boss.
S-U-B.
Thank you for explaining.
You honor me.
I'll continue to do my utmost
to be the perfect sub.
Yo, did you hear that?
Right, one last thing.
Hmm? What is it?
Masachika-sama also said that
you are still the most important
person in the world to him.
Yuki-sama?
Close call! I nearly screamed out
my love for him in the middle of school!
My dearest brother sure knows
how to tug at my heartstrings.
That aside...
He's really set on taking me on, huh?
Nice. Things are getting interesting.
Honestly, I didn't think Alya-san
would've put up much of a fight by herself.
Most of the first-years seem
to believe that you will get elected.
As for Kujo-sama... I hate to be blunt, but...
"She's being dumb 'cause she transferred
into our middle school after Suou's reign"
seems to be the prevailing opinion.
Wow, they're merciless.
Now, how does Onii-chan plan
to turn this situation around?
You seem to be enjoying yourself.
I am.
I get to go up against that prodigy—
the greatest talent the Suou family
has ever produced.
Onii-chan, who I could never best at anything,
is coming at me with
a formidable partner, Alya-san!
It's enough to make the heart sing!
Now we're talking!
Bring it! I'll take you on with all I've got!
By the way, Ayano.
What is it, Yuki-sama?
Wasn't I giving off some major
final boss vibes just now?
Student Council Office
I raise.
Fold. I'm out.
Oh, really?
All I had was a high card.
I guess bluffs do work.
What?!
Oh no, Alya-chan.
That's too bad.
Looks like Suou's got the upper hand there.
New
Student
Council
Members
Welcome
Party
It's a battle of wits,
and that's Yuki's playground.
I'm sure that's part of it,
but I feel like Alya-chan's
simply too easy to read.
Sarashina-senpai...
I was trying not to say it out loud.
Oops. Sorry about that.
The younger Kujo doesn't have
much of a poker face, does she?
I kind of assumed
she would be a lot more composed.
On the contrary, the elder Kujo
might be the one who's hard to read.
Ah, yeah.
I can't really tell
what she's thinking, either.
She's a great girl, almost a paragon of virtue,
but she does the strangest
damn things from time to time.
She's got her own special energy.
Or just, like, she's a ditz?
Again, I was trying not to say it!
Sorry again.
Sarashina-sama.
Whoa!
Would you like a refill?
You really snuck up on me.
I'm good. I've still got some.
Understood.
You have a unique way of carrying yourself.
Did you pick that up serving as Suou's aide?
Yes. My grandparents taught me.
Oh?
Her grandparents used to serve Yuki's family.
Wow. Your parents, too?
No, my parents are office workers.
Wait, what?
Yes.
I chose this because I admired my grandparents.
It isn't the family business or anything.
Huh... How long have you been doing this?
There was no clear start date.
But I believe I decided to follow
this path back in second grade.
Early, much?
That's how much I admired my grandparents.
And also, it was Masa—
massively clear to me that Yuki-sama
was someone worth serving.
Ayano, a moment.
I apologize for my slip-up, Masachika-sama.
Uh, it's fine as long as
it doesn't happen again.
But...
Knightly
Idolization
Her eyes are filled with love and respect!
Why? Is she not mad at me anymore?
What the heck did I do
to score points with her?!
Is not making a sound
a required skill for an attendant?
Indeed. My grandparents drilled it into me.
They said a servant must never stand out.
Ayano-chan, can I get a refill too?
I apologize for not noticing, Mariya-sama.
Alya-chan told me to shut up and go away.
I'm starting to get worried.
They won't get into a fight, right?
Don't worry about it.
It looks like Alya's enjoying herself.
She's really letting her hair down for once.
I know, right?
Oh, you can tell?
I sure can.
She's enjoying herself?
Looking like that?
Oh, are we out?
I should go get more.
I'll go.
Don't worry about it.
You're the heroine of today's show.
This welcome party is for the two of us.
As the girl, I guess
that makes you the heroine.
Exactly.
Would you lead the way, hero?
Why am I not exempt?!
New Student
Council Members
Welcome Party
We're going on a drink run. What do you want?
I'll have a café au lait.
The brown one, not the white.
Oshiruko, please.
Witsuya Cider for me.
Cola—or actually, ginger ale.
I'm fine with water.
Er, I'll have some lemon tea.
You didn't have to say. You're coming with me.
Oh, right you are.
Uh, so Witsuya Cider, ginger ale, lemon tea...
the brown café au lait, oshiruko, and water.
Gotcha.
Thank you again, Kuze-kun.
Where did that come from? For what?
For offering to run with Alya-chan.
I'm sure she was delighted.
Maybe, but it's not something
you need to thank me for.
You think? I very much disagree.
Alya-chan has never had anybody to lean on,
so I'm glad you're there for her now.
Okay...?
Wait...
Hmm?
I just had a thought.
Are you deliberately hiding
your responsible side from Alya?
You see, I don't want to compete with her.
She's a real hard worker, always going
full-throttle in everything she does.
And I love her for that.
What are you doing?
So you're playing the role of her
counterpart, a happy-go-lucky older sis?
I'm not exactly "playing" anything.
It's just, living life with the dial
constantly turned to 11 can wear you out.
We all need to relax a little.
Though, I won't deny that I do try
to be extra lax around Alya-chan.
I don't want her to feel isolated.
Sister relationships are complicated.
All sibling relationships are, actually.
We're the closest people
in the world to one another,
and that forces us to compare and compete.
Yeah, I'm painfully aware of that.
I only get away with
not feeling inferior to Yuki
because she has no qualms in showing
her love and admiration for me.
Café Coffee
Milk au Lait
Is she putting on a crazy otaku persona
on purpose to act like a stupid little sis?
Nah, that's definitely
just who she is deep down.
I see you're a caring older sister, Masha-san.
Aren't I?
I actually am a great big sis,
believe it or not.
But keep it a secret from Alya-chan, okay?
Why would I tell her?
Even if I did, she probably
wouldn't believe it.
She'd have to be convinced that her sister's
secretly a mature, responsible person.
Please. You act like you're
not hiding a responsible side yourself.
Unlike you, I don't have a good reason for it.
I'm just looking out for myself.
I just play the slacker so I can take it easy
and not have people depending on me.
Don't pay it any mind.
There, there.
Good job hanging in there.
It'll all be okay.
You'll be just fine, Kuze-kun.
I'm not really...
Good boy. A good boy needs praise.
I don't get it.
Why is it so easy for her
to break through my shell?
Kujo Alisa-san?
Sorry, I know this is abrupt.
I'm Taniyama Sayaka from Class F.
Can we talk?
Taniyama Sayaka?
She's the one who was Yuki-san's
election opponent back in middle school, right?
Kujo-san.
Is it true that you're going to run
with Kuze-san in the presidential election?
It is. What about it?
That's a pretty classless move.
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Huh?
You stole the running mate
Suou-san had set her eyes on.
Was it to spite her?
Wh-Wha?
What are you implying?
That I did something underhanded
to get Kuze-kun to back me?
Am I wrong?
I don't know how you did it, and I don't care.
But you picked that massive slacker
to be your running mate,
and I can only assume
you did it to spite Suou-san.
No!
Alya? And Taniyama?!
What's the matter?
Don't ask me.
She's accusing me of pulling some
shady crap to steal you from Yuki-san.
The heck?
Uh, Taniyama?
I don't know what you heard
or who you heard it from.
But I made the decision
to run with Alya myself.
I find that hard to believe.
You'd been going through
the motions for so long.
What gave you the motivation to team up
with this transfer student here?
"Going through the motions"?
I guess you're not exactly wrong.
Either way, Yuki's accepted my decision.
Whatever you think happened, you're wrong.
If you said something untoward to Alya,
could you please apologize?
I see now. So you're the one in the wrong here.
Kuze-san. I challenge you to student congress.
What?
Did you hear that?
We're getting a student congress.
For real?
What's happening?
Two presidential candidates
are gonna have a student congress!
Wait, hold on a second. Are you serious?
Why would I joke about this?
Someone like you has no place
in the presidential election—
no, on the student council in general.
Hold it right there.
I've heard that a student congress between
candidates can establish a pecking order.
In that case, I need to be
part of this conversation.
Stay out of this. You're just a puppet
with good grades and nothing else.
We're running as a team
in the presidential election!
If you, as a candidate yourself,
want to take down Kuze-kun,
you'll have to go through me!
And here I was trying to
spare you the embarrassment.
Very well. I'll take you both down
in one fell swoop.
People like you two don't deserve
to run for president.