Sometimes
in Russian
Hides Her
Feelings
Alya Sometimes Hides
Her Feelings in Russian
Episode 8
Student Congress
So, the topic for the student congress debate
is "Introducing Teacher Screenings for Student Council Entry," huh?
Laser-targeted at me. I don't have
much of a rep among the teachers.
Are you really going to do this?
I feel like there's nothing in it for you.
There is something.
If we can beat her,
our candidacy gains legitimacy.
Also, she insulted Kuze-kun and myself.
I need her to take back
what she said and apologize.
Yeah?
Hey, it's not all bad.
It's a chance to introduce ourselves and
our candidacy ahead of the closing ceremony.
If you say so.
Very well. We'll announce it by end of day.
Allow me to draft
the announcement, President.
Please do, Suou.
Good luck, Masachika-kun, Alya-san.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Going off what I know about her,
Taniyama's likely to use this line of argument.
I see.
How would you counter that?
Yeah, this is good.
It could stand to be a bit more concise, though.
Say, Kuze-kun.
Are you and Taniyama-san on bad terms?
Nah, I'd like to think not.
I feel like there was a mutual
respect when we worked together.
Yeah? Then why did she do all that?
Who knows?
Maybe she thinks I'm entering
the election to make a mess of things for fun.
What gave her such a negative
impression of you to begin with?
Well, I used to be Yuki's partner.
But I quit working with her,
the odds-on favorite,
to pair up with someone else.
I don't blame her for doubting my motives.
But that's...
It's all because I teamed up with him.
I brought this on.
I...
Alya? What's up?
I'll make sure we win tomorrow.
Yeah, let's do that.
Been a while, Kuzecchi.
Let's have a good one.
Wait, me saying that is a bit weird.
Do you think you're here
for a picnic or something?
Well, I'll have nothing to do
during the actual debate.
I'll basically just be chilling.
Heya, I'm Miyamae Nonoa.
Sayacchi's running mate, for what it's worth.
Hi, I'm Kujo Alisa. Let's have a good debate.
Whoo, really got that game face going, huh?
I think you and Sayacchi might just get along.
That's Taniyama-san's partner?
Yeah, and childhood friend, apparently.
Polar opposites, but they're best friends.
I see.
Miyamae's one of the most
popular people in school.
She's got connections
that rival the cream of the crop.
That's a powerful asset in any election.
Not something you need to
worry about today, though.
Stay focused on Taniyama.
You're right. Got it.
Thoughts on today's topic?
I could go either way.
Taniyama-san was our queen's election
opponent back in middle school, right?
She transferred in?
Yeah, all I know about her is
that her grades are good.
Can I really do this?
Won't I get ignored like last time?
No, I have to.
This is also for Kuze-kun,
who agreed to be my running mate.
Can she even manage a speech?
Taniyama-san's gonna run away with this.
...ya.
Alya.
Kuze-kun?
Alya...
Is it true you're an E-cup?
Mm?
Wha?
You perv! I-Is this really the time?!
No better time than now, actually.
You can't hit me right now, can you?
Die.
Looking at me like I'm human garbage?
Does that help ease your nerves?
Alya, who are you going up against?
Taniyama-san, right?
Wrong. Your opponent is the idealized,
perfect version of yourself.
You don't need to be perfect.
Just do whatever you think is cool.
Don't worry. I'll work things out
if it comes down to it.
It's time.
We will now commence the student congress.
The proposers of the motion are
Taniyama Sayaka and Miyamae Nonoa.
Kujo Alisa and Kuze Masachika
will be the opposition.
The topic is, "Introducing Teacher
Screenings for Student Council Entry."
Proposer, you may now state your case.
Right.
As things stand, student council officers are
chosen by the president and vice president.
But the reality of it is,
they accept any and all entrants.
A survey of former student council
members confirmed that
So, it's who you know?
this has indeed been the case
over the past three terms.
I guess?
Seriously? She even collected data for it?
Wait, no. This must've been Miyamae's doing.
I believe that our student council
must be comprised of a chosen few.
And I'm sure you would all agree.
The moment they become a student council
officer, even a low-performing student
stands above you in
the school's societal hierarchy.
Are you really okay with that?
Damn, she's good.
Individual students don't care, but she made
them care by shifting things to their POV.
And so, I propose introducing
teacher approvals as a prerequisite.
That will allow only those
recommended by teachers,
the truly talented individuals,
to make up our student council.
We need to bring about a more exclusive
student council, one we can all respect.
So I ask for your support.
Thank you for your time.
Opposition, you may now make your case.
Right.
How will she turn this around?
Not happening. Taniyama-san's already won.
Let's hear what our
ice queen has to say, at least.
"Do whatever I think is cool," huh?
I think I'll do just that.
I'm Kujo, the student council treasurer.
I will represent the student council
in presenting my opposition to this motion.
Taniyama-san stated that
introducing teacher screenings
would bring about a student
council that we can all respect.
However, I believe it would do the opposite.
It will only infringe on
the student council's authority.
After all,
this motion involves stripping
its president and vice president
of their right to nominate their officers.
Those two positions hold the highest authority
and respect within the student council,
because the student body
chooses them by popular vote.
And they, by virtue of winning
a highly competitive election,
are granted several privileges by the academy.
Chief among them, the right to
choose their own officers.
It wouldn't be right to hand over even
a portion of that to the teaching staff.
Wouldn't it be tantamount to saying
the student council, as it stands,
can't function as it should
without the help of the teachers?
This academy prides itself
on respecting the students' autonomy.
That is exactly why a great amount
of power is vested in the student council.
What do you think happens if all of its
officers have to be approved by the staff?
The president and vice president
won't be able to recruit students they trust.
They also won't be able to refuse
any recommendations by the teachers.
Okay, she's staying composed up there. Perfect.
That means the teachers
will essentially hold all the power.
Both Taniyama and Alya's arguments are valid.
But the student council exists to
represent the student body, does it not?
I'd say the students are currently split.
I didn't put her up to this, Taniyama.
These are all Alya's words, not mine.
Thank you for your time.
We will now commence the debate.
Very well.
Go ahead.
As I mentioned earlier,
the student council has accepted
every single volunteer recently.
And that hasn't caused any issues,
so what problem do you have with it?
I believe it's vital to introduce teacher
screenings to prevent downturn in performance.
It should be up to the president
and vice president to make that call.
They have the option to accept their
shortcomings and ask the teachers for help.
It's not something
the rest of us get to decide.
You mistook who you were up against.
Alya's been your opponent all along,
but you've only been focusing on me.
Now, what's your move?
Then what if the president and
vice president abuse their power?
Well...
But Kujo-san's an outsider
at the end of the day.
What would a newcomer know about our academy?
Taniyama-san's got this in the bag.
Tch, classy move right there.
Plants, huh?
Huh?
Well?
Wait, what was I about to say?
Oh no... I need to respond, and quick.
But what do I say?
Good job. Let me handle the rest.
Excuse me. I'll be taking over from here.
I guess her vocal cords
couldn't handle all that talking.
This is what you get
for never talking to people.
Well, I'd like to finish this off quick
so my partner can rest.
I ask you, do we even need to debate this?
Huh?
What is he saying?
I believe you already made up your mind
when you elected President Kenzaki over there.
You all know that he was a slacker
who barely made an impression in class.
Actually, let me cut to the chase:
He was the kind of dweeb who'd never get
the teachers' approval in this hypothetical.
But President Kenzaki put in the work.
He upped his grades, worked on himself,
and went from loser to
worthy presidential candidate.
And you all voted for him because
you wanted to cheer him on, right?
He was only able to become
student council president
because our system allows for anyone with
the drive to become a student council officer.
So I ask you again:
Do we even need to debate this?
Uh, I'm still processing
the sudden bullying by my junior,
but if there are no further questions,
we will move on to closing statements.
Is that all right, proposer?
Huh?
Wait, Sayacchi?
Alya?!
'Kay, we accept defeat!
Huh? Uh...
Can we take that to mean
you're withdrawing the motion?
Yeah, that's fine.
Sorry for this mess my Sayaka caused.
The motion has been withdrawn.
That concludes this student congress session.
Take it away, Masachika-kun.
You got it, Yuki.
When I saw those two together,
I thought I'd come upon the perfect duo.
The two of them had each other's backs
and absolute trust in each other.
I realized that they had
a bond stronger than any other,
and that I never stood
any chance of beating them.
It helped me accept my defeat,
though I was left feeling a tiny bit envious.
And that's why...
When I saw those two together,
I felt betrayed.
Wait up!
Why? Why did it have to be you?!
Kuze-san and Suou-san were special!
I made my peace losing to them!
I gave up on my goals because it was them!
So why you?
If you have anything else
to say, let it all out.
I have no right to say anything.
I feel like such a fool.
I put them on a pedestal
and put all my faith in them,
and then felt betrayed and took it out on you.
But I'd just made it all up in my head.
Oh, there she is.
Aw, look at you, crying up a storm.
Sorry, Kujo-san.
I'll take it from here.
Uh...
It's fine.
Please, let me.
Taniyama-san, even I don't know
why Kuze-kun chose me.
But I want to ensure he made the right choice.
So I'll give it my all...
And maybe one day, you'll say
it was the right choice, too.
That's all.
Man, Kujo-san's such a good gal.
I'm sure.
After all, Kuze-san chose her.
Better apologize to Kuzecchi and her
once you've calmed down, okay?
I'll go with you.
My brother is such a softie.
He could've put an end to this farce
any time he wanted, but he didn't.
Whatever. They won't be much of
a challenge if that's all they've got.
Their lack of killer instinct
will prove to be their downfall.
Don't you agree?
Are you sure?
I thought Masachika-sama and
Kujo-sama put in a fine performance.
Ayano.
Yes?
You don't get it! Not one bit!
We gotta ooze confidence with, like,
shadows shrouding our eyes,
and condescendingly judge our opponents!
That is how you give off boss vibes!
I apologize for my lack of knowledge.
Yeesh, get your act together.
Why do you think I took on the sound and
lighting job when it gets so hot in here?
Loyalty
If I may, can I ask you a question?
What is it?
Isn't giving off boss vibes a trait
of characters who ultimately lose?
Also, as I said before, food and drink
aren't allowed in this room.
Ayano, let's pack up.
Understood.
Taniyama-san said...
That you and Yuki-san were special,
and that she put you on a pedestal.
And that's why she was able to give up.
Oh.
I'll give it my all. You have my word.
I'll prove that you made
the right choice to run with me.
And I'll prove it to Taniyama-san, too.
Yeah, I better put in the work, too.
Say, can I ask you something?
Why did you choose to run
with me and not Yuki-san?
I ran with Yuki because I couldn't
bring myself to turn her down.
Of course, part of me wanted
to support her in her pursuits.
But my guilt was probably the biggest factor.
Your guilt?
Maybe that's why I felt so trapped back then.
Compared to the people around me,
all working toward their hopes and dreams,
all I had driving me was guilt—
and it was pathetic.
I kept putting myself down, again and again.
They called me the VP
pulling the strings in the shadows,
but, the truth is,
I just didn't wanna be in the spotlight.
Things are different this time around, though.
I decided to run for vice president
because I wanted to.
Because I wanted to be your running mate.
So, yeah, it's not a question of
weighing Yuki and you.
It's, like...
Well, you get the point.
You were supposed to put it in words there.
Shut it!
I see you smiling! You're not getting
another word outta me!
And heck, how about you?
What about me?
Why are you running with me?
Oh, that's obvious.
Потому что это ты.
The heck does that mean?
We should get going.
Yes, ma'am.
By the way, Kuze-kun, what was that about?
What do you mean?
That stuff about my chest size.
O-Oh, that? Uh...
A girl I know said something
to that effect once.
She claimed that you were
probably around an E-cup.
Correct, just barely.
Huh? Barely?