I can't stay focused.
Brain Hazard airs soon.
No, no anime breaks.
I know I won't return to studying after that.
Exams start tomorrow, okay?
Welp, it's on now.
Wow, I've become such a scatterbrain.
I've forgotten how to put in the work.
Plug away, man.
Gotta at least make sure
my rep doesn't affect Alya's standing.
Huh?
Alya
Decline
Accept
Alya?
Sometimes
in Russian
Hides Her
Feelings
Alya Sometimes Hides
Her Feelings in Russian
Decline
Accept
Alya
Oh, hello?
Episode 10
Birthday Party, Much Belated
Good evening, Kuze-kun.
Yeah, hey there. Something the matter?
I didn't call for a specific
reason or anything.
What's up? Did you miss me that badly?
Is that a problem?
What was that thud?
Nothing. So, how can I help you?
Well, you said you're prone
to slacking when you're alone.
So I was wondering if you were
studying like you're supposed to.
Nope. I can't stay motivated.
I'd like to know how you
keep it up at times like these.
"Keep it up"?
No idea. I don't lose
motivation to begin with.
Seriously? That's crazy.
If you're having trouble staying focused,
why don't we make a bet?
Bet?
What's your goal for these exams?
I'd like to place in the top 30 for our year.
Aiming big, are we? Well, that works.
If you manage to hit that goal,
I'll do one thing you ask for—anything.
Hm? Anything, you say?
Within reason, obviously.
What do you say?
What if I don't hit the goal?
You'll do one thing I ask for, of course.
Kinda does things for me, to be honest.
Kuze-kun?
Wait, I wasn't implying I wanted to be
ordered around in a masochistic way or anything!
Given name.
Huh?
I just gave you a hint.
Not much of a hint when you say it in Russian.
Heh, I know that.
Anyway, do we have a deal?
Yeah, you're on.
I'm gonna make you regret offering that bet!
Oh, I'd love to see you try.
You've gotten better at ignoring my outbursts.
You're making big bro cry.
Since when have you been my big bro?
We're the same age!
Huh? Isn't your birthday November 7th?
It is... How do you know that?
I think you mentioned it in your
class introduction when you transferred in.
Anyway, that's not important.
My birthday is April 9th.
I've already turned sixteen.
Anyway, thanks for checking in, Alya.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah, see you.
I can't believe she realized I'd lost focus.
Are our minds linked or something?
I called because
I got spooked by a horror show.
No chance I was telling him that...
But what the heck?
Why didn't he tell me his birthday?
I would've celebrated it with him!
Didn't he say we were friends?
Kuze-kun, you jerk.
Five Days Later
Finally done!
Good job powering through exams, Alya.
Yeah, you too.
3. Modern Lit.
Lunch Break
Intro Chem
Uh, do you have any plans after school?
No, not particularly.
Wanna walk partway home together, then?
I'd like to discuss what we're doing
for the closing ceremony.
Sure.
Something's wrong.
She hasn't flirted with me in Russian
once since that phone call.
So, you wanted to talk about
the closing ceremony speeches?
Yeah... but first,
haven't you been acting kinda
different since the exam period started?
I thought I'd made sure it didn't show.
It pretty much didn't, actually.
But I could just tell.
R-Really? So you cared enough
to pay that much attention to me, huh?
Even during exam period?
Of course I care. You're my partner.
O-Oh?
Then why?
Your birthday...
Huh?
Why didn't you invite me
to your birthday party?
My birthday what?
I didn't have a party. Who told you I did?
You didn't have one?
You expect me to believe that?
Huh?
O-Oh!
Is it commonplace for people to have
birthday parties in Russia?
Y-Yes?
Is it not in Japan?
Dunno about everyone else,
but I haven't had one since elementary.
Oh...
Oho? You wanted to celebrate
my birthday with me that badly?
In Russia, leaving someone
out of your birthday
sends a clear message that you're done
playing nice with them from that year forward!
Oh, yeah?
What?!
Nothing. I'll spare you
from any further embarrassment.
Oh, buzz off!
Guess we should celebrate it together, then.
Three months late, but I do want us
to play nice this year, too.
There you have it. I'll be throwing
a belated birthday bash.
Be there or be square.
What the heck?
Kuze-kun.
Did I keep you waiting?
It's so hot.
Good thing we're not in uniform.
Those long sleeves are killer.
True.
The president's trying to introduce
a short-sleeved summer version, right?
Right.
But even if the proposal goes through,
it'll probably be introduced next year.
Wow. People are seriously doing double-takes.
What?
Oh, I just noticed that
we're drawing a lot of attention.
Ignore it. It's the price
I pay for being so beautiful.
You probably get hit on a lot
when you're alone, huh?
Yeah. People keep approaching me on weekends.
Yep, called it.
How do you deal with it?
I ramble in Russian until they go away.
I see...
Phew. I was afraid she was fighting them off
with violence—verbal and physical.
Did you just think
something very unflattering?
'Course not.
Just glad you're not letting any sleazy
pick-up artists sweep you off your feet.
Oh, is that a hint of possessiveness?
Acting like my boyfriend now, are you?
Well, excuse me.
I tend to wanna act like the boyfriend
when on a date, at least.
You don't say.
A date, huh? Right...
It's my first.
Yeah, I guess this is your first date with me!
I mean, there's no way this hottie has never
been on a date before, right?
TGIBeef Steakshack Jr.
Is this the place?
Yep.
Dinner here gets pretty pricey,
but at lunchtime, you can try a bunch of
different meats for a reasonable price.
Smooth choice, if I do say so myself!
This—
This place is great.
I've come here with my family before.
I remember thinking the venison was delicious.
Oh...
Ahem.
Okay, lemme give you a rundown of
how the closing ceremony plays out.
Sure.
First, the presidential candidates
lay out their motivations and policies,
and then their running mates talk about
why they're backing him or her.
Now, here's the crucial part.
This event doesn't feature any formal
polling, but it has something similar.
What?
After each pair speaks
comes the audience reaction,
and the people in the audience
only applaud for the pair they want to win.
Uh, you mean some candidates could be met
with nothing but pin-drop silence?
Does that happen?
It does.
Yikes.
Frankly speaking, it's hard to see us
getting a reaction like Yuki will right now.
So our goal should be
to keep the gap manageable.
No need to try to beat her.
An awfully passive approach.
It's a realistic assessment
of the current situation.
Fine, I understand.
Also, we should try to make our speeches first.
The first pair usually gets a muted response
as the crowd weighs up their options.
So we'll have a ready-made excuse
even if Yuki shows us up.
Don't give me that look.
We do have some other options,
but they'd involve taking the gloves off.
Like what?
Like playing mind games
on Yuki and Ayano, maybe?
But that wouldn't sit right
with you now, would it?
It wouldn't, no.
It'd be a different thing
if they tried to start something,
but I bet even they
wouldn't go that far.
Not like they're Miyamae.
What do you mean?
Here's your order.
Well, uh, here's to my birthday, I guess?
Cheers!
Cheers.
This is delicious.
It is.
Were you the one who started
that rumor about Miyamae-san?
Hmm?
Oh...
She found out halfway through student congress
that I had plants in the audience.
Y'know how it goes.
Nope, that was all her.
She even started it herself.
Really?
That put a stop to
all the shit talking about Taniyama,
but it also put the outcome
of that student congress in limbo.
Sorry. There might've been
a better way to do that.
No, it's fine.
I didn't contribute anything. I couldn't.
I have no right to complain.
Thanks for doing that for me, Kuze-kun.
Sure, don't mention it.
What? Is that a blush I see on your cheeks?
Shut it.
You're so cute.
Whoa! She's not even hiding it
behind Russian anymore!
Here, as a token of my appreciation.
Say aah.
Oh, look. Somebody's overconfident.
She only gets aggressive
when she thinks I'm flustered.
Did she forget how she couldn't
use the spoon after the last time?
Thanks. That was great.
Yeah?
Wha? She's unfazed?!
She's got me right where she wants me.
Great meal.
Thanks for that.
Let me give you your gift.
Huh?
Here you are.
You actually got me something? Thanks.
Whoa!
Talk about a fancy mug! This is really nice!
Isn't it?
Thanks. I'll put it to good use.
Yeah, you do that.
Hm? What?
Uh, I just figured cups like this
are stuff couples buy in pairs.
Aha, so you do get it.
Of course I bought two.
I'm already using mine at home.
Seriously?!
So...
What would you think if I said that?
You know what?
She's really got me figured out today.
Student Council Office
While we await our turn
for the parent-teacher meeting,
I'd like to discuss
the summer uniform proposal.
Okay, let me make some tea.
Yes, please.
Oh, you sit back and relax, Ayano-chan.
Kuze-kun? What's the matter?
Oh, nah, it's nothing.
So, Prez, do you have an update
on the summer uniforms?
Yeah.
Keep it between us, but I think we can
introduce the new uniforms after summer break.
Wait, really?
Yeah. We're going to make a surprise
announcement at the closing ceremony.
That's wonderful news.
As much as I like this uniform,
it gets too hot at this time of year.
So thank you.
Thanks for saying so.
But Chisaki played the biggest role
in getting this proposal approved.
I wouldn't say that. You did this
by not letting up in the negotiations.
Chisaki!
Toya...
It's amazing how easily those two
can enter their own little world.
Okay, tea is ready.
Here you are.
Thank you, Masha-san.
S-Sure.
Still bothered by the hypnosis
from last time, huh?
Looks like my parents are here.
I'll head out for the parent-teacher meeting.
Good luck with that.
I'll clean up.
Oh, let me help.
I'll take you up on that.
Uh, Masha-san?
Hmm?
I want to apologize.
For the whole hypnosis thing.
No, it's fine. I started it, anyway.
And, uh... well...
There's something I wanted to ask you.
While I was hypnotized,
what did I do to you... exactly?
Er...
You pulled me and Alya into your arms...
and gave us head pats.
Huh?
Is that all?
Yeah, pretty much.
Oh, I'm relieved to hear it.
With that said,
did you, uh... see?
Kuze-kun, you perv.
Sorry, it was kind of unavoidable.
So even Masha-san gets mad about this stuff, huh?
But...
She's not the least bit scary.
If anything, she's positively adorable.
Kuze-kun?
Yes, ma'am?
Are you actually sorry?
Whad ar' you 'oing?
Punishment for a bad boy!
Listen, you can't embarrass
a girl like that, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, that'll do.
Oh, looks like Mom's here.
You should go.
I'll handle the rest of the cleanup.
Can I ask you to do that?
Of course. Good luck.
Sarashina-senpai and Alya-san are gone, too.
Yeah?
We're finally alone, just the two of us.
Guess I should go pick up Grandpa, too.
Wait up!
Why are you ignoring me?!
Look who's talking!
You're acting like Ayano isn't here, too!
You're being so cold! It's been a while
since we got some sibling time!
I guess it has, actually.
I guess you didn't care because
you were off having fun times with Alya-san.
Hey, it's not like that,
you... know?
Sniff, sniff. I was so wonewy.
Yeah? You were wonewy, huh?
Be a good girl and get off the desk, okay?
So, yeah.
Spoil me!
What is with your mood swings?!
What's the holdup? I don't have all day.
You want it... here?
That's right. I'm telling you to spoil me
right here and now, Masachika-kun.
I... understand.
Come to me, my little kitten.
Never mind! I'm done!
I was just kidding!
You were so cool, big bro!
Grandpa
Oh, Grandpa's here.
Grandpa?
Hey, Masachika. There you are.
What's with the white suit?
Don't I look dapper?
Only peak narcissists and Western mafia
would dress up like that!
Oh, right.
I forgot to put these on.
There. Aren't I dashing?
You really donned those sunglasses!
Okay, what movie influenced you this time?
Actually, why'd you even have this stuff?
I used my pension to buy it all for today.
Grandma's gonna have a word with you.
Kyotaro too busy to make it?
Well, he just got moved to
the Japanese embassy in England this year.
He probably has a lot on his plate.
He could at least make time
to meet your teachers.
It is what it is.
You're such a good kid.
Cut it out!
We'll be going now.
Thank you very much, Sensei.
Shoot!
Oh, Kuze-kun...
An Eastern European miracle!
Stop that!
Sorry about that, Alya!
This is my grandpa,
and he's a bit too obsessed with Russia!
Huh? Oh... is that so?
May I ask your name, miss?
Seriously, you stop that right now!
Uh... your grandfather seems very spry.
So, you're Kuze-kun?
That's me. Nice to meet you.
Would you be Alisa-san's mother?
My, such a polite young boy.
Nice to meet you too.
I'm Kujo Akemi, Alisa's mother.
She's told me lots about you.
Good things, I hope.
Oh, she positively beams
when talking about you.
Does she now?
Miss.
Would you like to join our family?
H-Huh?
Hey, behave!
What do you say to marrying
my boy Masachika here?
Shut your damn mouth!
Is that all right with you, Masachika?
Again, shut up.
So?
Are you going to marry Kuze-kun?
Quiet, Mom.
We'll be going now.
Thank you for your time.
So, let's talk about this Alisa-san.
Can we drop that topic... already?
Hey.
It's been too long, Yumi-san.
Indeed it has,
father-in-law.