Look, Mother! I got a perfect score!
You did great. That's very impressive.
Oh...
So that's not enough to satisfy her.
I need to really excel if I want to
make Mother truly happy.
Stop it!
Please, just stop.
I dredged up some bad memories...
Okay, yeah, this is not good.
I've caught a cold.
Sometimes
in Russian
Hides Her
Feelings
Alya Sometimes Hides
Her Feelings in Russian
Episode 11
An Unexpected Curtain-Raiser
Yes?
Huh?
Alya? U-Uh...
Did Yuki tell you?
Yes. She asked me to bring you
some medicine since you'd caught a cold.
Oh, yeah?
That punk! Give me a little notice!
May I come in for a bit?
Huh? You don't have to.
Just the medicine is fine.
Yuki-san asked me to nurse you, okay?
Don't drag innocent strangers into your
otaku fantasies, sister of mine.
Well, that's not true.
It was a false accusation, sorry.
Pardon me.
Oh?
No need to be so wary.
I-It's not like I'm nervous.
It's just... This is all very new.
And it smells of boy in here.
That's not the kind of thing
you want to say in a whisper!
Anyway, so...
What would you like? Porridge or borscht?
What's with the selection?
Hey, borscht is really good for you.
The veggies are boiled until tender,
so it goes down smoothly even when you're sick.
Okay, okay. I'll have the borscht, then.
Got it. Give me around four hours.
Nope, not waiting that long.
Using a pressure cooker would
speed things up, but that's blasphemy.
Regular old porridge it is, then.
Very well. Let me use your kitchen.
Let's see... If I use pre-cooked rice...
Search recipes
Egg Porridge w/ Chicken Stock (using pre-cooked rice)
Requires around 12 minutes. Approximately 230kcal (one portion).
Oh, I have to heat it in the microwave, huh?
He's using it.
Oh, uh, where was I?
Kuze-kun, your porridge is ready.
Whoa...
My deepest thanks for
gracing me with the apron look!
I see you're doing better than I thought.
Think you can eat?
Probably.
Here.
Thanks.
This is yummy.
Yeah?
Um...
Where are your parents?
Dad's at work. No mom.
Oh, we're a single-father home.
Oh, is that so...
Thank you. That was great.
No problem. Did you take your medicine?
Yeah.
I'm gonna go back to sleep.
Feel free to leave whenever.
It's fine. I'll be studying in the living room.
Uh, you don't have to...
You're sick. Worry about yourself first.
Yes, ma'am.
Damn, talk about oversleeping.
Alya must've left by now, surely.
Should you be up and about, Kuze-kun?
How are you feeling, Masachika-sama?
Go ahead and lean on me.
H-Hey!
This looks like I'm pulling
my maid into my arms!
Gotta be careful in this day and age.
I might get canceled.
What are you talking about?
Anyway, get away from him, Kimishima-san.
I will not. This is part of a maid's duties.
But you're Yuki-san's maid, not Kuze-kun's.
Yuki-sama ordered me
to look after Masachika-sama.
As such, this falls under my duties.
You can let me take over from here.
It's getting quite late. Go home, Alisa-sama.
Hey! Phrasing!
Besides, shouldn't you be
preparing for tomorrow?
Huh? What's tomorrow?
Nothing. Just school.
I'll be on my way.
Take care of Kuze-kun, please.
Of course. You can count on me.
See you, Kuze-kun.
Yeah, see you.
Alisa-sama made borscht for you.
Right.
Here you are.
Thanks.
Let's dig in.
This is great!
Whew. That was amazing.
Your medicine, Masachika-sama.
Oh, thank you.
Eating's made me sleepy again.
Will you be bathing tonight?
Hmm? I think I'll pass.
Allow me to wipe you down, then.
Yeah, no.
Don't worry. I'll use a blindfold.
How are you going to
wipe me down blindfolded?
It's fine. Let me just go back to sleep.
I'll sleep next to you, then.
Chill!
At least let me sing you a lullaby.
No need for that!
Stare.
Stare...
Ayano?
Yes? How can I help?
Go back to Yuki's and call it a night.
That's an order.
Understood.
Good night.
Yeah.
I should've played that card right away.
Morning.
Good morning, Masachika-sama.
Seriously? I super overslept again!
You skipped school for me?
Your health matters far more
than some flimsy report card.
How are you feeling?
A lot better.
Glad to hear it.
I'll prepare lunch right away.
Thanks. That'd be great.
Thank you for the food.
Your appetite is back.
However, you should
take it easy today, just in case.
Oh, well...
School's done for the day, anyway.
Your medicine, Masachika-sama.
Yeah.
Thank... you?
Hmm? Something's bothering me. What is it?
Is something the matter?
Ayano, let me see this medicine's package.
Ayano?
Understood.
This drug contains shit that'd
make me sleepy, doesn't it?
So it would seem.
Why didn't you warn me if you knew?
I apologize.
I've committed a grave error
in offering you incompatible medicine.
You may discipline me in any way you see fit.
Was it Yuki who told Alya to get me this?
I'm going to school.
You should stay home.
I'll be fine.
However, I must say...
What is it?
I believe it is too late.
What?
Our queen really is amazing.
Yeah. Lady Alya did what she could,
but she's a cut above.
Dammit! I was too complacent!
I assumed she wouldn't try anything
until the closing ceremony.
I didn't expect her to make her move now!
Alya.
Kuze-kun...
What happened?
I'm sorry.
I messed it all up.
I've wasted all your help.
I...
It started yesterday morning.
Yuki-san asked to talk to me.
Student Council Office
Kuze-kun's down with a cold?
Yes. Normally, I'd be the one
to go check on him,
but I have something else to take care of.
Oh... Okay, I'll go.
You will?
In that case, here's the cold
medicine he always takes
and his address.
If you would, please.
Got it. I'll drop by after school.
There is one other thing I wanted to discuss.
What?
Would you mind making a guest appearance
on the lunchtime PA broadcast tomorrow?
Huh?
I was thinking of covering
the recent student congress tomorrow.
Tomorrow...?
Yes. It's a good opportunity to really
drive home your victory in the debate, no?
I'm sorry, but I have no intention
of bringing that topic back up again.
Oh, is that so?
Then...
Forget that part, then!
Would you please appear anyway?
Huh?
We can make our final
progress report for the first term!
How does that sound?
O-Okay, that's more acceptable.
Yes! Thank you so much!
You two are truly set on not taking advantage
of that student congress victory, huh?
You figured it out?
How could I not? I heard the recent
rumors about Nonoa-san's cheating.
Just the fact that you're
letting it spread tells the whole story.
Dearie me.
Awfully laid-back, aren't you, Alisa-san?
Are you even trying to beat me?
What...?
Do you not sense any danger at all
in waltzing into my territory?
I must say, you're sorely lacking
in survival instincts.
You're such a sitting duck
that I just had to give you a warning.
There's more to the guest appearance?
You finally caught on?
It's happening right when Masachika-kun's
out sick. You should be more wary.
You're trying to take advantage?
Indeed. I wish to use this opportunity
to crash your stock as much as possible.
You think you can toy with me
as you please as long as I'm alone?
You belittle me far too much.
Oh, feel free to run to
Masachika-kun for help.
No need. I will not be a burden to him.
Really, now?
Let me see what our ice princess
can do tomorrow, then.
I will not be beaten.
I prepared for it as best I could, of course.
But then, after school ended today...
I'm terribly sorry, Alya-san!
What exactly are you apologizing for?
I'm apologizing for the attitude
I took with you yesterday.
I felt terrible about scheming
against a dear friend like this.
So I took an overly aggressive stance
in order to force myself to go all-in.
I'm fully aware of how
self-serving this may sound,
but I do not wish
to sour our friendship, Alya-san!
I-It's fine. Raise your head.
May I take that to mean
that you accept my apology?
Y-Yeah. It just goes to show
how serious you were.
Thank you so much. I'm so glad to hear that.
This may sound like an excuse,
but there's a reason why I must
become president no matter what.
What reason?
I used to have an older brother.
He was far more talented than I could ever be,
and our parents and grandfather
expected great things from him.
They were certain that he would take
the Suou name to greater heights.
But one day, he was gone.
I must live up to my family's hopes
in my brother's place.
It is my duty to finish what he started.
Ah.
It's almost time.
Are you ready?
I am...
But, before that, how about you?
Huh?
Why do you want to be
student council president?
Uh... well...
It's time. Let's begin.
Good afternoon, everyone.
This is Suou Yuki,
student council spokesperson,
here to bring you another progress
report on the student council's activities.
We have a very special
guest joining us today.
Kujo Alisa here.
The student council treasurer...
Er, it's my pleasure to be here today.
First-time nerves, I suppose?
It was the same after that. I was a total mess.
Yeesh, that's devious.
She acted like the bad guy to fire Alya up,
only to bring out the sob story
before going live.
"I'm carrying the hopes of my entire family
on my shoulders. How about you?"
I'm so mad at myself.
I was so easily shaken,
and I couldn't recover...
Stop right there.
Your thoughts are spiraling in a bad direction.
What do you mean?
I'm saying you're playing into Yuki's hands.
Her goal wasn't to take the lead
using today's broadcast.
Just think about it.
We only had school in the AM today.
There weren't many students
remaining in school.
If she wanted to assert her dominance,
there were better times to do it.
You mean she was simply laying
the groundwork for the closing ceremony?
Precisely.
She just wanted to throw you off your game.
I bet she was hoping to
leave you down in the dumps.
And here you are, mad at yourself.
Okay, I get it. Thank you.
Why are you smiling?
Hmm?
Wow, I am, huh?
Nah, just thinking she got us good.
I don't really know why,
but this is giving me goosebumps.
That look suits you too... I like it.
I didn't have an answer.
To what?
I couldn't answer her when she
asked me why I wanted to be president.
She's going into the election
to win it for her family,
but I'm only doing this for myself.
And I couldn't bring myself to tell her that.
I'm ashamed of myself for wavering.
I hate that I couldn't answer her
with my head held high!
Chin up, Alya!
Your motivations aren't
as noble as Yuki's? So what?
Remember what I said before?
You're a perfectly
captivating person as you are.
I know fully well how driven
and how earnest and hardworking you are.
So...
Keep your chin up. You're fine.
Your charms do not pale in comparison
to Yuki's in any way whatsoever.
I promise you that.
That sounded almost like you were
professing your love to me.
Shut it! I'm never doing
that again, seriously!
Sheesh, I feel so hot!
My fever's coming back!
Thank you. You helped me
regain my confidence.
Yeah? That's good.
You're right. There's no point
comparing myself to her.
Yep.
Even if Yuki-san's carrying on
her dead brother's spirit...
Hey, sister of mine!
You made her think I'm dead!
L-Listen, Alya...
Heya.
Wait, didn't you take the day off?
Excuse me.
Oh, I just got here.
Yeah?
Close your legs, Nonoa.
What's the big deal?
Not like anyone else is here.
So, what do you want?
I know this is belated, but Kuze-san, Kujo-san...
I apologize for my actions
and my appalling behavior.
I'm truly sorry.
My bad, too. I should've stopped her.
Might be too late for that,
but could you please forgive us?
That's for Alya to decide.
All I wanted was an apology
for those insulting remarks.
As for you, Miyamae-san,
you didn't even do anything to apologize for.
Uh, I think using plants
definitely merits an apology.
Did you not bring up the congress
on the broadcast to protect my reputation?
I didn't want to declare myself victorious
when I didn't defeat you in debate.
I see. You're very prideful.
But so am I.
Hold it, Taniyama. What are you thinking?
Facts are facts, my reputation be damned.
So, what? You're gonna
go declare your own defeat?
With a PA broadcast?
No, at the closing ceremony?
Sorry, but as student council officers,
we can't let you run wild at the ceremony.
If you want to repay Alya's goodwill in kind,
could you do it another way?
What do you suggest?
Are you serious?
Yeah.
I'm not backing you two or anything.
I still think you should go back
to Suou-san's team.
Yeah?
But there's a reason I chose Alya.
And I bet you're starting to see it, no?
Fine.
No frickin' way!
'Kay, count me in too.
Thanks. Looking forward to it.
See, Alya? This is what you do.
Now we can beat them.
Huh? Beat them?
I thought we were aiming for a draw?
Nah, screw that.
They fired the first shot.
So now we gotta destroy them.